[
  {
    "question": "When looking at the digital marketing landscape which of the following are types of social media platforms available to users? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Messaging platforms",
      "Discussion platforms",
      "Collaboration platforms",
      "Sharing platform",
      "Publishing platforms",
      "Networking platforms"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following did Meta acquire to increase connections and communication between Facebook users?",
    "answers": ["WhatsApp"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true about Instagram?",
    "answers": ["Businesses can promote content through paid advertisements"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true about Facebook and Instagram messenger?",
    "answers": [
      "Businesses can use messenger to make suggestions, assist in sales, and offer support to customers in one continuous conversation",
      "Messenger lets businesses instantly connect with people on their Facebook Page or the Messenger app"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false: Many social media platforms, such as Facebook, offer special tools for non-profit organizations.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How does digital marketing differ from traditional marketing? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "It can be used to raise brand awareness",
      "It can be used to target specific audiences",
      "It enables measurements of results"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "As a business owner, you’d like to set up a presence on a social media platform where you can post videos and images as well as update customers on upcoming sales, new products, and events. Which of the following would be an ideal platform?",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Youtube is a platform designed for texting, calling, and sharing.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which social media platform has a powerful tool called Ads Manager that allows companies to create a specific and targeted ad campaign?",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "On Twitter, you can purchase advertising packages for which kinds of accounts? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Business accounts", "Personal accounts"]
  },
  {
    "question": "On which video social media platform can you find short form videos of 15 and 60 seconds?",
    "answers": ["TikTok"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Every message on WhatsApp is automatically encrypted.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which feature on Instagram can you use if you want to upload a video longer than 60 seconds?",
    "answers": ["Instagram Video"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following are NOT part of the SMART goal framework?",
    "answers": [
      "Social - how will you integrate it into the community where it’s done?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following goals fit the SMART framework? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Get 5,000 website visits in the month of June",
      "Increase the number of visitors to 100/day in two months",
      "Increase revenue by 25% by the end of the year",
      "Gain 20 new followers on the Facebook page by the end of the month"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Successful KPIs should:",
    "answers": [
      "Directly relate to the business and the SMART goal you drafted",
      "Be quantitative (able to be measured)",
      "Be directional (able to go up or down)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maria set a SMART goal for her chocolate business: “Increase the amount of new followers on the business’ social media page by 20% by the end of 3 months”. What would be a good KPI for her to use when evaluating if she is reaching this goal?",
    "answers": ["Brand awareness (number of people who know about your brand)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an important quality of a KPI?",
    "answers": ["Directly related to your goal", "Measurable", "Directional"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of a marketing KPI? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Brand awareness",
      "Cost per lead",
      "Sales revenue",
      "Conversion rate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Devon set a SMART goal for his hand-knit sweater business: “Gain 20% more new customers by the end of the year”. What would be a good KPI for him to use when evaluating if he is reaching this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "Conversion rate (how many people took action, e.g. bought something, out of the people you attracted)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla and Ivy set a SMART goal for their B2C flower business: “Grow the number of customers for the monthly flower bouquet subscription by 20% by the end of the year”. What would be a good KPI for Calla and Ivy to evaluate to see if they are reaching their goal?",
    "answers": ["Subscriptions"]
  },

  {
    "question": "All of the following social media data can help you determine your target audience except:",
    "answers": ["Page visitors’ social security numbers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT part of the Customer Journey template?",
    "answers": [
      "Love: How can I get my customer to feel a deep emotional attachment to my product?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: When outlining your target audience, you should consider audience needs, interests, and demographic data.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Will just saw an Instagram ad for a sweatshirt claiming to be the comfiest sweatshirt ever. In which stage of the customer journey is Will?",
    "answers": ["Awareness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Depending on the stage a person is in, different types of messages will work better than others.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do marketers use to represent the process of moving people through the customer journey?",
    "answers": ["The marketing funnel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: A customer journey refers to the process a user goes through when purchasing a product.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The following goal fit the SMART framework: “Increase the number of visitors to 150/day in three months.”",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following research tools allows you to view insights about your audience for multiple social media platforms? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Linkedin Audience Insights", "Meta Business Suite Insights"]
  },

  {
    "question": "You’re looking to do visuals-first advertising online. Your go-to social media platform should be:",
    "answers": ["Instagram"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are a fashion brand looking to create an immediate avenue for shopping. Your go-to social media platform would be:",
    "answers": ["Instagram"]
  },
  {
    "question": "IBM works with employee bloggers, training them to advance the company's goals and corporate reputation. Which of the following is part of “IBM’s Blogging Policy & Guidelines”? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "You must make it clear that you are speaking for yourself and not on behalf of IBM.",
      "IBMers are personally responsible for their posts. Be mindful that what you write will be public for a long time — protect your privacy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Determine whether the following statement is true or false: When an employee posts from a personal account, it is not important that they use the appropriate tone and messaging.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the three core values that a social media policy should achieve, which category does the following statement fit in? “Nordstrom encourages participation by reinforcing that employees will be compensated for their work.”",
    "answers": ["A social media policy must empower its employees"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following a quality of a website or a blog? There is a transactional functionality.",
    "answers": ["Website"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which benefit of blogging is the following an example of? When a business creates quality key-word rich blog posts frequently, it gives search engines fresh content to add to its database",
    "answers": ["Search Engine Optimization"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Determine whether the following statement is true or false: It is mandatory to fill out the Skills & Accomplishments section of your LinkedIn profile.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements about marketing and advertising are true? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Advertising is an important part of marketing",
      "Advertising is where the largest portion of the money spent on marketing goes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are the most common forms of digital marketing? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Social media marketing",
      "Display advertising",
      "Email marketing",
      "Content marketing",
      "Search engine optimization"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT involved in organic social media marketing?",
    "answers": ["Buying targeted ads to reach potential customers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: YouTube directly hires all its video creators to create content for the site",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which social media platform(s) has the most powerful targeted advertising software? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Instagram", "Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which social media platform is the best for connecting business to business (B2B) marketers to new customers and followers?",
    "answers": ["LinkedIn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "On which social media platform should you set up a business page to reach the largest audience?",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following specifies what you want to achieve, and helps to make sure that you and the people you are working with are all aligned?",
    "answers": ["A goal"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When writing your SMART goals, it is important to remember to make them measurable. Which of the following definitions best describes the meaning of a measurable goal?",
    "answers": [
      "A goal that can be evaluated in a quantifiable way, like for instance number or sales, revenue or number of visitors to a website."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: It is important to write down your goals.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After a successful year of business, Sheryl wants to expand her makeup and skin care business by opening up two more locations in her town. She decides to set a goal to open up both locations within 12 months. During the expansion process, she encounters difficulties. This is because her goal was not time-bound.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },

  {
    "question": "True or False: Your target audience is the group of people you want to reach with your marketing message.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When determining your target audience, it is good to write down the demographics of the people you are targeting. These demographics include which of the following? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Household income",
      "Gender",
      "Age",
      "Education and/or occupation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Meta Business Suite Insights can precisely determine who’s interacting with your page and give you real-time data when you test different marketing strategies.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Twitter Business Analytics is similar to Meta Business Suite Insights, but solely for its own business platform.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },

  {
    "question": "When you are focused on brand building, what kind of social media platform can help the most?",
    "answers": ["Publishing or sharing platforms"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you are focused on generating sales or sales leads through social media marketing, what kind of social media platform can help the most?",
    "answers": ["Platforms that offer immediate shopping integration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you are focused on providing customer service, what kind of social media platform can help the most?",
    "answers": ["Messaging platforms"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you are focused on building an online community, what kind of social media platform can help the most?",
    "answers": ["Collaboration or networking platforms"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Your brand should do which of the following? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Create a personality or identity for your business",
      "Differentiate you from your competitors"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you create a social media page for your business, you should always include which of the following? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": ["A link to your website", "A profile picture"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following components does a brand consist of? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "the words and voice the company uses",
      "products and services",
      "a logo",
      "principles",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a function of the brand? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "signaling device",
      "foster loyalty",
      "ease selections",
      "enable recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following components of the EPIC framework does the following statement encompass? How a brand connects with its customers through the written word",
    "answers": ["Connection"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a part of a brand’s existence?",
    "answers": ["Organizations that the company donates to"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which voice would be most fitting to connect with the following audience? Corporate CEOs looking for a succinct summary of business trends",
    "answers": ["formal and serious"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What major social media platform leads in business-to-business [B2B] interactions?",
    "answers": ["LinkedIn"]
  },

  {
    "question": "A good way to get people to engage with your Facebook post is: (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Connect with the reader on a personal basis",
      "Identify a problem and offer a solution"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Every Instagram post needs to contain a “hard sell” for your product.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you’re posting a photo in an advertisement, what are some things you should do? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Follow the Rule of Thirds", "Make sure your lighting is good"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tweets with video typically net how much more engagement than those without?",
    "answers": ["10 times as much engagement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Instagram only permits you to upload one photo per post.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "To show your Facebook post to an audience outside your followers, you should:",
    "answers": ["Use Facebook’s “Boost Post” feature to turn it into an ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about the use of images on social media?",
    "answers": [
      "A tweet with an image gets 3 times more engagement than a tweet with only text"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about videos on social media?",
    "answers": [
      "It is best to try to capture your audience’s attention in the first 5 seconds",
      "The ideal video length on Youtube is 2 minutes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which softwares below are social media schedulers you can use to manage and moderate your posts?",
    "answers": ["Buffer", "Hootsuite"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What elements should you include on your content calendar?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first thing to be done when starting to storyboard?",
    "answers": [
      "Determine your engagement goal (i.e. educate, increase traffic, make a sale, etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla and Ivy receive a comment from a customer named Amélie on their Facebook page. It reads: “Hey Imra—I loved my bouquet but I think it introduced termites into my home. I need to talk to you.” How do you respond?",
    "answers": [
      "“Hey Amélie—we’re sorry to hear that. That’s not in line with our standards, and we’ll DM you now to talk about this.”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Admins have total control of a Facebook page and are the only class that can assign and change others’ roles.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Joseph has a piano tutoring business and holds lessons for his students at his studio most days during the week. He likes to post videos of his student’s progress and playing tips to his Facebook page for his followers. He has plenty of videos and content to be posted, but has trouble remembering to post. When he does post, engagement is inconsistent. Which of the following tips should he apply to his social media strategy to better manage his page?",
    "answers": [
      "To help with scheduling posts, Joseph should look into using publishing tools."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: When responding to customer comments, it is important to take any issues and criticism of the brand out of the public sphere and address customers in private messages.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Every social media post must be new, unique content.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are part of the “Five Steps to Build Your Social Media Following”? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Invite your friends and family to follow your page",
      "Create an advertising campaign"
    ]
  },

  {
    "question": "Please be sure to expand the \"Instructions\" tab shown above to access the content calendar needed to answer each question. Take a look at Imra’s blog post promotions. Which post created the most readership on the website, and why might this have created the most traffic?",
    "answers": [
      "The personal story post created a lot of traffic because the personal story created more of a personal connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra has started posting about the bouquet creations she makes for her clients, in order to showcase the flowers and her skills, which will hopefully draw more people to order something they haven’t seen before. Which bouquet creations posts are receiving lower engagement?",
    "answers": ["Bouquet creations featuring only images"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra has started a Flower of the Week post, to help educate her followers about the different types of flowers out in the world. Unfortunately, engagement has been pretty low. Which options below could improve engagement? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Add a link to the website",
      "Post on a different platform",
      "Post at a different time or day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra noticed a jump in new followers on Facebook on May 11. What could be a reasonable cause of that?",
    "answers": ["The Fair Trade Day content blog post on May 11"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla & Ivy is going to be hosting some summer classes on floral arrangement, and Imra has posted twice about it, once on May 20 and once on May 27. What are some ways that Imra can gain more audience members for future promotional posts? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Include all the information, such as class titles, descriptions, and dates.",
      "Post at a different time of day."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In honor of Fair Trade Day on May 13, Imra wanted to create some content to raise awareness around fair trade flower farms. Take a look at the blog post promotions from May 11, 12, and 13. What could be a lesson to take into future posts?",
    "answers": ["Including a video creates higher web traffic"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra has started sharing articles to Twitter she thinks her audience may find useful, but engagement hasn’t been great. You notice that she hasn’t been including a mention (@) of the account or publication where she found the articles to her posts. Why is that a concern?",
    "answers": [
      "It doesn’t alert the original poster that something they created has been shared, so that they and their audience become aware of and can engage with Calla & Ivy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra makes a note of the important holidays throughout the month of May which might prompt her customers to make a purchase of her flowers. For each holiday, she has planned a post with a link to her website and a purchase page. Based on the data, we can see that the Mother’s Day post received the most engagement, including the most click-throughs to the purchase page. In addition to Mother’s Day being a more popular holiday for buying flowers, what is another possible cause for the higher engagement of this post?",
    "answers": [
      "A reminder of the holiday was posted a few days prior to the post"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Considering that Calla & Ivy’s audience is on Facebook during the mid- to late-afternoon, how is Imra doing on her posting schedule?",
    "answers": [
      "Pretty good! Most posts are between that time, but Calla & Ivy is still seeing good engagement from posts outside of the time frame."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which platform has the highest engagement for Calla & Ivy?",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },

  {
    "question": "What are the elements of a business social media profile?",
    "answers": [
      "Name, Username, Contact information, Description, Call-to-action (CTA)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What would be a good choice for a Facebook business page profile picture?",
    "answers": ["The business logo"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good descriptive keywords to include if you’re setting up an Instagram account for a coffeeshop? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Coffeeshop", "Coffee", "Espresso"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your social media cover photo should be:",
    "answers": [
      "An image that tells people something about your business, like one of your products, a behind-the-scenes photo, or a reference to a current ad campaign."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re designing a Facebook business page for a startup flower company. Which of the following should you use as your business’s profile picture?",
    "answers": ["Your company logo"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you’re a company that sells a physical product, like flowers, bike parts, or dog treats, what should your Call-to-Action button say?",
    "answers": ["Shop Now!"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: In order to create an Instagram Business account, you must switch a personal Instagram account to a Business account in the settings.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Write a brief description (3-4 sentences) of why the platform you selected is appropriate for your business.",
    "answers": ["oke"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Does your account or page include a business image, name, and category?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Does your account or page include a cover photo (for Facebook pages) or one post (for Instagram accounts)?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Does your account or page include a description detailing what the company does and how to contact the company?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },

  {
    "question": "In what ways can a company use social media to engage with customers? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "By sharing stories of the business and employees in a relatable and identifiable way",
      "By posting content that shows customers that the company is present and responsive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: You can add a hyperlink url to the caption of your Instagram post.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Pinterest is the best app to use if you want to exclusively post videos",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the rule of thirds? Select the best answer.",
    "answers": [
      "If you break up your image into thirds, horizontally and vertically, your subject matter should be at the intersection of one of the gridlines."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you want your Facebook post to be seen by an audience outside of your followers, you can turn it into an ad by selecting which option?",
    "answers": ["Boost Post"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Does your post include text?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Does your post include an image?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do the text and visual tell a cohesive story to the audience?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Write a brief paragraph describing your top three key takeaways from this module on Social Media Content and how they influenced your approach to this project on creating a Facebook or Instagram post. By “takeaway”, we are referring to important or useful information you have learned",
    "answers": ["oke"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following categories does engaging social media content typically fall into when trying to create value for our audience on social media, and create posts that will keep them engaged? (Select correct answer)",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When coming up with new content that's engaging, informative, or fun, there are many different topics you can post about. Which of the following are examples of the different kinds of posts you can create for your page? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "A video from the perspective of an employee showing followers what it’s like to work at your business.",
      "A social media takeover by an influencer for a day."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: The first thing to determine when starting to storyboard is your engagement goal for our social media post and what story you’re going to tell.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: When you create a content calendar you save time and stress, but you should not tweak it as you go so that you keep to your original goals regardless of engagement or audience reaction.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },

  {
    "question": "In the Content Ideas tab, is there at least 1 content idea in each content category?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Content Ideas tab, are there at least 8 content ideas across all categories?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Content Ideas tab, are all content ideas related in some way to the same business?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Week Calendar tab is there at least 1 piece of content from each of your content categories?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Week Calendar tab are there at least 3 pieces of evergreen content?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Week Calendar tab are there at least 4 pieces of content on your week-long calendar overall?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },

  {
    "question": "On Facebook, marketing goals typically fall into three categories. Which of the following is NOT one of these categories?",
    "answers": ["Page Views"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: On the Overview summary page, Facebook allows you to check insights for individual posts.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Three conversion metrics that are important to track include which of the following? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Website visits from social media",
      "Sales resulting from social media",
      "Number of leads resulting from social media"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "From the dashboard on the left navigation in Facebook Insights, you can explore which of the following?",
    "answers": ["All the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Review Imra’s blog post promotions. Which post created the most readership on the website, and why might this have created the most traffic?",
    "answers": [
      "The personal story post created a lot of traffic because the personal story created more of a personal connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra has started posting about the bouquet creations she makes for her clients, in order to showcase the flowers and her skills, which will hopefully draw more people to order something they haven’t seen before. Which bouquet creations posts are receiving higher engagement?",
    "answers": ["Bouquet creations featuring questions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra has started a Flower of the Week post, to help educate her followers about the different types of flowers out in the world. However, these posts are seeing very low engagement. What could be a reasonable cause of the low engagement?",
    "answers": ["She is using the wrong platform"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra noticed a jump in new followers on Instagram on May 28. What could be a reasonable cause of that?",
    "answers": ["The “How to: Tend Summer Garden” story was shared many times"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla & Ivy is going to be hosting some summer classes on floral arrangement, and Imra has posted twice about it, once on May 20 and once on May 27. What are some ways that Imra can gain more audience members for future promotional posts?",
    "answers": [
      "Include all the information, such as class titles, descriptions, and dates.",
      "Post on a different platform."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra started posting “How to” Instagram stories for various topics and noticed that her followers were very interested in these, based on the number of shares and impressions. She is planning her next “How to” Instagram story videos for the following month, and wants to use her insights to determine which topics her followers would most be interested in. Which topic should she choose?",
    "answers": ["Color schemes for bouquets", "Home Gardening"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the importance of including a mention (@) of the account or publication where Imra found the articles to her posts?",
    "answers": [
      "It alerts the original poster that something they created has been shared, so that they and their audience become aware of and can engage with Calla & Ivy."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Considering that Calla & Ivy’s audience is on Instagram from 1-3 pm Pacific Standard Time mid- to early-afternoon, how is Imra doing on her posting schedule?",
    "answers": [
      "Pretty good! Most posts are between that time, but Calla & Ivy is still seeing good engagement from posts outside of the time frame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the difference between Generative AI and Machine Learning?",
    "answers": [
      "Machine learning analyzes data to make predictions, while Generative AI creates new content."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Natural language processing is best suited to do which of the following types of generative AI?",
    "answers": ["Writing a professional email"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an ethical concern you should be aware of when using Generative AI?",
    "answers": ["Creation of deepfakes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which business case is generative ai least suited for?",
    "answers": ["Reaching new customers."]
  },

  {
    "question": "Did you successfully write an email response using Meta AI?",
    "answers": ["Yes!"]
  },

  {
    "question": "How does Generative AI support social media marketing strategies?",
    "answers": [
      "By analyzing data to understand audiences and generate engaging content."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How can Generative AI be used to understand your target audience?",
    "answers": [
      "It synthesizes large datasets to create detailed audience profiles."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of using Meta Advantage tools in ad campaigns?",
    "answers": ["They automate campaign setup and optimize ad performance."]
  },
  {
    "question": "How can Generative AI tools enhance social media content creation?",
    "answers": [
      "By generating text, images, and videos based on simple prompts."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Did you create a social media post complete with the text component and the image component using Meta AI?",
    "answers": ["Yes!"]
  },

  {
    "question": "The section where you write clearly and concisely what you want people to understand and remember about your offering is which component of a social media ad?",
    "answers": ["Copy!"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re running ads for a company that creates and sells art through a webshop. Which of the following Facebook Call to Action buttons should you use to get people to purchase a piece of art?",
    "answers": ["Shop Now"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re creating an ad for a boutique smartphone case company called Case. The target audience is design-conscious people aged 21-39, with an interest in modern art and minimalist home decor. Your ad creative is a photo of a child looking pensively over the ocean. Your copy reads: “You’re stylish—shouldn’t your phone be, too?” Your CTA says “Shop Now!” Which part of the ad is ineffective?",
    "answers": ["Creative"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? People read ads on their mobile screens beginning to end, so your Facebook ad copy should be as long and detailed as possible.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Alexa owns a nail salon and wants to incorporate multiple before and after images into an ad campaign on Facebook showcasing her salon’s work. Which of the following ad types would best suit her needs?",
    "answers": ["Carousel Ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Effective social media ads should always include which of the following? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "A clear offer",
      "A Call-to-Action",
      "A corresponding destination (often a landing page)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true in regards to how paid advertising may benefit a business? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Paid advertising can help you increase your follower count.",
      "Paid advertising can help you market your business’ goods and services.",
      "Paid advertising can help you reach a specific audience that you may not be reaching already with your organic social media efforts."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Social media ads are very accessible and allow you to create your own campaigns.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are ads you create directly from organic posts already on your Facebook page called?",
    "answers": ["Boosted Posts"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Twitter’s Card ad formats are specific image or video ads that drive users to take a certain action. Which of the following formats do Card ads come in? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["App Card", "Website Card"]
  },

  {
    "question": "An ad agency submits a creative brief to you. It looks almost complete, but it’s missing a description of who you want to engage and influence. Which creative brief element is missing?",
    "answers": ["Target audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You need someone to create the visual assets for your campaigns. You’re looking to hire a:",
    "answers": ["Designer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re writing a creative brief for your company and want to share information to make your offer more credible and trustworthy. What is the name for this component of a creative brief?",
    "answers": ["Proof points"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If you have a Designer on your team, you will usually not need a Brand Manager as the designer can take care of the logo and brand designs.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your ad objective or goal is to bring people to your online store and ultimately sell them your product. Which KPI will be most important for you to measure?",
    "answers": ["ROAS (Return on Ad Spend)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Your objective determines your Key Performance Indicators (KPIs).",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? You typically don’t need to ask users for their permission before you take their images and use them as visuals in your ad.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You should organize the copy of your ad into three parts. Which of the following is NOT one of those three parts?",
    "answers": ["Conclusion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Emojis can be an effective way to grab their attention and communicate in a casual way.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following are GDPR citizen rights? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Citizens have the right to correct their information",
      "Citizens have the right to have all the information that was collected and saved about them erased",
      "Citizens have the right to access the personal information received about them"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? COPPA is an extension law to CCPA?",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following data categories are companies prohibited to collect under the GDPR?",
    "answers": ["Ethnicity", "Sexual orientation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the acronym for the law that gives residents of California more insight into what data is collected about them, and was passed in 2020?",
    "answers": ["CCPA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If an advertiser or publisher enrolls in the DAA’s YourAdChoices program they are automatically compliant with GDPR or CCPA.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are European self-regulatory principles for Data-Driven Advertising?",
    "answers": ["Education", "User choice"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Data-based advertising enables advertisers to display ads to people based on their location or previous behaviors.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Meta’s Data Policy clearly outlines which of the following information? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "What information is received from users",
      "How information is used",
      "How users can manage and delete their data",
      "Contact information for people who have questions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are on Facebook and see an ad for a clothing brand that seems very specific to your particular taste. You decide to click the three dots at the top right corner of the post and use Meta's ad tool to be informed on who the advertiser is trying to reach based on their audience targeting information. This tool is called:",
    "answers": ["“Why You're Seeing This Ad”"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Let’s say you have a food magazine that you’re promoting an Instagram post for. Your goal is to build a larger following on Instagram to eventually grow your business. Your promoted post should direct users towards:",
    "answers": ["Your Profile"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you’re advertising a new restaurant on Instagram. You want your ads to be seen by people with similar interests as your current followers. Which advertising targeting option should you use?",
    "answers": ["Automatic targeting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "To keep your stories dynamic, you should:",
    "answers": ["Break them into multiple scenes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the first step in creating an ad campaign with Facebook Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Choosing your ad objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You start a Facebook Business Page and want to run an ad to increase people’s awareness of your business and get more Page likes. Which Facebook Ads Manager objective should you choose?",
    "answers": ["Promote Your Page"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you run a shop in Atlanta that sells disc golf equipment . You haven’t started your online store yet so you want to drive people to your physical location. Which Facebook Ads Manager objective should you choose?",
    "answers": ["Promote Your Business Locally"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When creating an ad on Facebook, you can target specific demographics, interests or behaviors.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your business is hoping to get in contact with more of their customers directly. In order to achieve that goal, what should they do?",
    "answers": ["Include a CTA Send Message button on an ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What action would a business want its customers to take if it selects “Boost A Post” as its campaign objective when creating an ad on Facebook?",
    "answers": ["Like a post"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following are true about paid advertisements on social media? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "They are labeled as sponsored",
      "You can control where and when your ad is shown"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are true about organic posts on social media? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Unless shared, they only appear directly in the feeds of people who already follow your business",
      "They are free to post"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what ways can Facebook and Instagram ads help grow your business?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Facebook and Instagram are the only social media platforms on which you can advertise.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },

  {
    "question": "The objective for your ad campaign is to promote awareness of your brand and get people to remember it. Which KPI will be most important for you to measure?",
    "answers": ["Ad Recall Lift"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The total revenue generated by an ad campaign divided by the total ad spend (how much you spend on the ad campaign) is the formula for which KPI?",
    "answers": ["Return on Ad Spend (ROAS)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: When designing videos for your Instagram ad campaign, you should design for sound on.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What two things should the opening of your ad copy accomplish? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Call out your audience", "Pique the audience’s curiosity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are tips for writing effective copy for your ad? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Change your tone depending on the channel or platform that you are using",
      "Try emojis",
      "Create urgency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a recommended way to source visual elements for your ads?",
    "answers": ["Look at what worked from your competitors and copy their work"]
  },

  {
    "question": "An ad for luxury bathrobes appears next to an article about how to create an at-home spa experience. Is this an example of contextual or data-based advertising?",
    "answers": ["Contextual"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You just purchased a new activity tracker and are now seeing ads for running shoes and workout gear. Is this an example of contextual or data-based advertising?",
    "answers": ["Data-based"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If a company that has no clear relationship with the company you are currently interacting with is tracking your data using browser cookies, what type of data are they collecting?",
    "answers": ["Third party data"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This can be created on websites where people have to log in. It is a unique number assigned to someone’s account and is associated with all their interactions and behavior on that website. What is this called?",
    "answers": ["UID"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Cookies can work across multiple devices and browsers.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following are details you can set when defining your audience on Facebook Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are steps in creating an ad campaign on Facebook Ads Manager? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Set a budget and campaign duration",
      "Choose an objective",
      "Set your target audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you just totally redesigned your business’s website and it works better than ever. You want to get more people to see the update that your website just got. Which Facebook Ads Manager objective should you choose for your campaign?",
    "answers": ["Get More Website Visitors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you just started a company that specializes in creating specialty jewelry. You put up a business page on Facebook and are hoping people will view it and start connecting with you there. Which Facebook Ads Manager objective should you choose?",
    "answers": ["Promote Your Page"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of an ad placement option for ads created on Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Profile"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of major ad placement places your ads in some articles on the Facebook mobile app?",
    "answers": ["In-Article"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the Meta total value ad auction equation covers feedback from people that view or hide your ad, as well as findings of “low-quality” attributes such as sensationalized language, engagement bait, and more?",
    "answers": ["Ad Quality"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say two skateboard companies are competing in an auction to show one person, named Daniel, an ad. Daniel lives in the mountains and loves hiking, snowboarding, and skateboarding. Company One targeted people who like skateboarding who live near the mountains in a few U.S. states. Company Two is targeting all men who like to skateboard in the U.S. Daniel has liked lots of posts on Facebook to do with the mountain sports near him. Which part of Company One’s Total Value score will this boost?",
    "answers": ["Estimated Action Rate"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following ad account settings helps you control your total ad costs and will pause your ads after a certain spending limit is reached?",
    "answers": ["Account Spending Limit"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? If your currency or time zone changes, you can update those in your Ads Manager settings.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT something you define when thinking about ad sets?",
    "answers": ["Objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the second step in the campaign-creation process in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Select your ad sets, which tell your ad how to run"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what Ads Manager business tool category would you find tools to prepare mockup ad campaigns?",
    "answers": ["Advertise"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Ads Manager’s Creative Hub lets you prepare mockup ad campaigns without actually running them.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which objective should be selected to generate sales on a website or app?",
    "answers": ["Sales"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A nonprofit is creating a newsletter and wants to optimize towards collecting email addresses to send it to. Which objective should the nonprofit apply?",
    "answers": ["Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which feature in Ads Manager allows Meta to dynamically assign budget to ad sets based on their performance, therefore maximizing your spending efficiency?",
    "answers": ["Advantage campaign budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you sell bike chains, which each cost $200. You have a revenue goal of $10,000. You know that one out of every 100 customers who visits your page buys one bike chain. How many people exactly need to visit your page for you to meet your projected revenue goal?",
    "answers": ["5,000"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which bid strategy limits what Meta can bid in every single auction?",
    "answers": ["Bid Cap"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which bid strategy does Meta recommend you select in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Highest Volume"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you’re doing a split-test, which variable should you change to test whether it’s more effective to optimize for impressions, leads, link clicks, or other options. ?",
    "answers": ["Delivery Optimization"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which variable in a split test compares how effective your ads are at reaching different audiences or demographics?",
    "answers": ["Audience"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which example below best fits the concept of a \"target audience\"?",
    "answers": [
      "A Boston Red Sox fan seeing ads for Red Sox and other Boston sports team apparel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The three audience types you can create in Ads Manager are Custom Audiences, Lookalike Audiences, and _____________?",
    "answers": ["Core Audiences"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An apparel company known for its line of t-shirts and hoodies is trying to boost an accessories line it launched last year, but they can't seem to get it to pick up. They know they have sales, and they know they have visitors to the product page, but they can't connect the two, and retargeting their core audience doesn't seem to be working. Why would installing the Meta Pixel be a good idea?",
    "answers": [
      "The Pixel will allow them to track events customers take — like website visits, start purchases, and completed purchases — so that they can create custom audiences and target audiences for their new product line"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A movie theater just opened in New York City. They show classic, foreign, and art-house films, and do theme weeks, film festivals, and actively promote local filmmakers, bringing them in for discussions of their films. You're creating a Core Audience for them. What criteria would you probably choose?",
    "answers": [
      "Location: New York City Age: 30-60 Gender: All Detailed Targeting: Filmmaking, Art Film, Movies, Short Films, Documentaries"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local bookstore has been in a town for thirty years, owned by one family. The daughter is now taking over the business. She has plans to upgrade the store’s website and create a social media presence for it. They do have a massive list of customers stored in their internal database from sales tracking and newsletter signups. How could they easily begin targeting their audience online using Ads Manager?",
    "answers": [
      "Upload all that customer data to create a Custom Audiences to begin targeting their audience online"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Often scheduling your ads is very useful, but it could also be harmful. In what way could it be harmful to your campaign?",
    "answers": [
      "It limits ad delivery and so you could miss out on conversions outside of your scheduled window"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A mobile app-based company wants to improve their advertising, and wants to start playing around with Manual Placements to see if that improves their return. Of the four responses below, which would be a good place to start?",
    "answers": ["Set their ad placements to Mobile only"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary goal of optimizing for \"landing page views\" in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": [
      "Show your ad to users who are likely to click the link and load the page"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’ve recently stepped in to run ads for an e-commerce business. They've run multiple ad campaigns, but saw a lot lower actions taken than they thought they would see. You investigate their Core Audience settings, and find the location set to three neighborhoods in San Francisco, the age set to 25-30, and just one detailed targeting criteria. What does this tell you?",
    "answers": [
      "They set their audience up too narrowly, so their Audience Size was too small, and didn’t get them the reach they needed."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A quick service restaurant client is launching a new delivery service and wants to build awareness of the service to a large number of people. The client wants to launch a campaign that reaches people ages 18-34 who are interested in food and dining. The client has two creatives: a ThruPlay video and a 6-second video. Which objective and placements should the client use?",
    "answers": [
      "Awareness objective on Instagram Stories, Instagram feed and Facebook feed"
    ]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which ad format is designed to reflect the way people actually consume video— from bite-sized videos they watch on the go, to longer video styles they watch on the couch?",
    "answers": ["Single Video"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A hardware business wants users to immediately be able to browse its pipe collection, which contains more than 25 types of pipe of varying lengths and widths. Which ad format should the retailer use to meet these requirements?",
    "answers": ["Collection"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser is looking to change an ad campaign’s objective from Sales to Traffic. Where should the advertiser navigate in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Campaign level"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? It’s a good idea to use stock photos when creating your ads as opposed to your own photos, as stock photos are more universal.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You design an ad for a campaign that markets skate shoes to teens. Is Meta likely to reject this campaign for violating its Ad Policies?",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a valid reason that an ad would be rejected by Meta?",
    "answers": [
      "The ad contained sexually suggestive images.",
      "The ad used a Facebook logo with a red background instead of the official blue",
      "An image within the ad focused on individual body parts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which KPI estimates how many people would remember seeing your ad if they were asked within two days?",
    "answers": ["Estimated Ad Recall Lift"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new menswear brand company delivers a campaign to generate maximum awareness among new potential customers. Which metric should the company use to evaluate the success of the campaign?",
    "answers": ["Reach"]
  },

  {
    "question": "What can public figures, businesses, brands, organizations and nonprofits create on Facebook to establish a presence and connect with an audience?",
    "answers": ["Page"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary goal of a Facebook group?",
    "answers": [
      "A space to communicate about shared interests with certain people on Facebook"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the minimum criteria a company must meet to receive the \"very responsive to messages\" badge?",
    "answers": [
      "A response rate of at least 90% and a response time of less than 15 minutes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a similarity between a boosted post and Facebook ad?",
    "answers": ["Both require budget to be shared with a wider audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is organic reach?",
    "answers": [
      "The number of people who have seen a post through unpaid distribution"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first step required to establish a business presence on Facebook?",
    "answers": ["Create a page"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which role for managing your Facebook page is the lowest class of permissioning and has access to audience data?",
    "answers": ["Analyst"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When can you include a dedicated link to your landing page?",
    "answers": ["When you create an ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what order is an advertising campaign created in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Campaign, Ad Set, Ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of budget in Ads Manager lets you control how much money you spend on each ad set?",
    "answers": ["Ad Set budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What action would a business want its customers to take if it selects Sales as its campaign objective?",
    "answers": ["Make a purchase"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you select Traffic as your campaign objective, what are you hoping your audience will do?",
    "answers": ["Visit your website"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the benefits of Meta Pixel? (Choose two)",
    "answers": [
      "Measures the results of an ad across devices",
      "Helps advertisers reach the right people"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two ad placement options are available on Instagram? (Choose two)",
    "answers": ["Feed", "Stories"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You design an ad campaign for a weight-loss product with “before and after” pictures. Is Meta likely to reject this campaign for violating its Ad Policies?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser wants to get a high-level view of how all of their campaigns are performing. Which level of Ads Manager should they view to see these results?",
    "answers": ["Ad account level"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A restaurant launches a video campaign for a new location. The goal is to maximize the number of times the video has started to play per impression. Which metric should be used to measure success?",
    "answers": ["Video plays"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the total value ad auction equation tells you the numerical score Meta assigns to an ad through the auction?",
    "answers": ["Total Value"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A car dealership wants to receive contact information on Facebook from potential customers to increase test drives. Which campaign objective is appropriate for this business?",
    "answers": ["Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand has a new goal to get more people to see, share, like and comment on individual posts on Facebook and Instagram. Which campaign objective is appropriate for this brand?",
    "answers": ["Engagement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to acquire new customers and increase sales. Which strategy should the business select?",
    "answers": ["Create a campaign with the Sales objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element is required to create a Custom Audience from website visitors?",
    "answers": ["Meta Pixel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who do businesses try to reach with a lookalike audience?",
    "answers": ["People who have a similar profile to an existing audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A retail business is launching a new shoe line with eight different style and color combinations. All styles must be shown to the audience. However, the business isn't sure which products will sell best. The business wants to link each style page directly to the product to receive pixel information. Which ad format should the retailer use to meet these requirements?\"",
    "answers": ["Carousel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an advantage of using the slideshow format instead of video when designing an ad for mobile?",
    "answers": ["It works well in areas with limited connectivity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: You must have a lifetime budget selected in order to set a specific ad set schedule (i.e. one with specified days and times).",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which variable in a split test compares how your ad performs with a video asset versus an image carousel, or with any other differentiation in ad-level adjustments?",
    "answers": ["Creative"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You have created a campaign with multiple ad sets and individual ads. You want to know the amount spent on a specific ad set. Where can this be found?",
    "answers": ["The Ad Set tab within Ads Manager in the Amount Spent column"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the difference between reach and impressions?",
    "answers": [
      "Impressions refers to how many times an ad appeared on a screen. Reach is an estimate of how many people saw an ad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which data protection law was specifically designed to protect children?",
    "answers": ["COPPA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which advertising tool on Facebook implements the simplest, and least detailed, way to create a Facebook ad?",
    "answers": [
      "Advertising from your Business Page",
      "Advertising from your Page"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two ad placement options are available on Instagram?",
    "answers": ["Stories", "Feed"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which major ad placement encompasses native, banner, interstitial, and rewarded video ads?",
    "answers": ["Apps"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Facebook advertising happens through an auction, rather than the more traditional route of paying directly for advertising space.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the Facebook total value ad auction equation covers how much an advertiser is willing to pay to achieve their desired outcome?",
    "answers": ["Advertiser Bid"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say two bike part companies are competing in an auction to show one person, named Marissa, an ad. Marissa lives in Portland, Oregon. She regularly buys her bike parts from internet start-ups with a Portland angle. Company One’s ads target all American women who cycle, whereas Company Two’s ads target cyclists who live in Portland with Portland-specific messages. Which part of Company Two’s Total Value score does Marissa’s purchasing history boost?",
    "answers": ["Estimated Action Rate"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which marketing goal group focuses on encouraging customers to purchase or use your product or service?",
    "answers": ["Conversion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which specific ad campaign objective promotes traffic to your brick and mortar store?",
    "answers": ["Store Traffic"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you choose the Traffic objective on Ads Manager, Facebook will show your ad to people who are:",
    "answers": ["Likely to click through to your website"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A car dealership wants to receive data information on Facebook from potential customers to increase test drives. Which ad objective is appropriate for this business?",
    "answers": ["Lead Generation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An animal shelter wants to raise awareness that there’s going to be an influx of pets from breeding season up for adoption. They specifically want to target people who have demonstrated online interest in animals and animal adoptions. Which ad objective is appropriate for this business?",
    "answers": ["Brand Awareness"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Why is targeting your audience important? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Better optimize your ad spend, time, and resources",
      "Find potential customers based on characteristics and behaviors who may be interested in your products or services",
      "Better match your customers and your products"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the types of audiences you can create in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Core Audience, Custom Audience, and Lookalike Audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What criteria categories can you adjust when you create a Core Audience?",
    "answers": ["Location, Age, Gender, Demographics, Interests, and Behaviors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following events can the Facebook pixel track?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are ways to create a Custom Audience? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Use data based on a person’s browsing history",
      "Use data from Facebook’s SDK installed on your app",
      "Upload a customer list",
      "Use data based on Facebook information, such as people who watch a specific video or people who have interacted with your Instagram profile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Custom Audience is better?",
    "answers": ["Typically a smaller, more specific audience is the best"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If a business wants to retarget customers who previously purchased an item from its website, what audience type should it use?",
    "answers": ["Custom Audience"]
  },

  {
    "question": "A business wants to sell products online. What ad format clearly displays both a video and a product?",
    "answers": ["Collection"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new nail polish company is creating an ads campaign for the launch of their new fall line with nine different colors. In the ad all new colors must be shown to the audience. However, the business doesn't know which new products will best sell. The business wants to link each style page directly to the product with a call-to-action purchase button. Which ad format should the retailer use to meet these requirements?",
    "answers": ["Carousel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Identity section, all ads are required to be associated with what?",
    "answers": ["A Facebook Page"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Ads Manager automatically shortens ad text depending on the placement your ad receives.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If, when you create an ad, your photo is too large for a square or horizontal format, you should:",
    "answers": ["Crop the photo"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following things could cause Facebook to reject your ad campaign while it’s in review?",
    "answers": [
      "“Shock and Scare” Violence",
      "Vulgar Language",
      "Sexual Content"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a valid reason that an ad would be rejected by Facebook?",
    "answers": ["The ad used before-and-after weight loss photos"]
  },

  {
    "question": "A business wants to evaluate their campaign, and specifically wants to look at how much net profit after investments they made versus how much they spent on advertising. This measurement would be:",
    "answers": ["ROI"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to evaluate how much they're spending on their customers, versus how much their customers go on to spend. If they want to see how much a customer will spend during the time they're a customer, that measurement would be:",
    "answers": ["LTV"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business is setting up a campaign, and is thinking ahead to which metrics they would want to track. Which KPIs would you track for an awareness campaign?",
    "answers": ["Reach, impression, or brand awareness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business gained 50 new customers in April, 100 new customers in May, and 150 new customers in June. During that time, they were running a campaign with a budget of $3000. What was their Customer Acquisition cost?",
    "answers": ["$10 per customer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company recently increased the price of one of their products. The product costs $1 to make, and previously they charged $5, but just increased the price to $7. If they spend the same amount on advertising ($1000), and sell the same amount of products (500) during a specific time period, how does their ROI change?",
    "answers": ["ROI goes from 2.5 to 3.5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing manager is attempting to collect data on their campaign. Where could they find information about how their paid and organic content did?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A college charges $10,000 per semester for tuition. If that college has two semesters per year, what is the student's lifetime value for a student getting a four-year degree?",
    "answers": ["$80,000"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business recently ran a conversion campaign, where they spent $1000 a month for four months. At the end of that time they had 800 new customers who purchased a total of $5000. What was their Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$5.00"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business is trying to get a better return on their ad spend — they've been hovering around 1.5 — and they're hoping this last campaign helped. It ran at $400 ad spend a month for three months, and they generated $1500 in revenue. How did they do?",
    "answers": ["Worse — their ROAS went down by .25"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business determined that they spent $50 to acquire a customer. What would be included in that amount?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Imagine you work in the marketing department of a large electronics company. You are planning to set up a new conversion campaign on Facebook focused on generating online sales for computer monitors. Your manager asks you to make sure you can report on the effectiveness of your campaign once the campaign is completed. The first section of the Brand Survey Test focuses on the test details. What are your options for what you can test? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "You can test the effect of all the campaigns that are running in your account together.",
      "You can test the effect of a group of campaigns.",
      "You can test the effect of a group of campaigns that have not run yet but you plan to run.",
      "You can test a specific campaign."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How might a Brand Survey Test on the Facebook platform help an advertiser?",
    "answers": [
      "It shows the incremental lift in ad recall caused by a brand awareness focused campaign, thus helping to evaluate the effectiveness of that campaign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If you want to run an experiment to test your advertising effectiveness, you have to plan it before you create and run your advertising campaign.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? A well designed experiment requires that people in the test are randomly assigned to the test or the control group.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The ‘control group’ is the group in the experiment that will be exposed to the treatment.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Meta pixel can track conversions made on what platform?",
    "answers": ["Website"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign's incremental impact is...",
    "answers": [
      "Any difference between the groups is likely to have been caused by the ad or campaign."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are running a marketing campaign for your fitness clothing brand company and your goal is to increase sales. Imagine you want to measure the effect of your advertising on conversions for your Facebook ad campaign. What kind of test do you want to run?",
    "answers": ["Conversion Test"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you ran a Holdout Test for your Facebook campaign and you find the following information in the report of the results: Conversion lift percent: 15.2% Conversion Lift: 2,155 Sales Lift: $88,100 Based on this information, which of the following is correct?",
    "answers": [
      "Your Facebook ads caused 2,155 additional conversions to occur that wouldn’t have happened otherwise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If the confidence level for your test isn’t very high, stop running your test for a bit longer and decrease your advertising budget to see a bigger effect.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },

  {
    "question": "True or false? You would run a marketing mix modeling study to show how your advertising on different platforms contributed to company sales.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you are planning a campaign for scented candles on Instagram. You have several images of the candles you want to promote, but you are not sure which image will work best. After a meeting with your team, you narrowed the choices down to two different images. One is an image of three candles on a dresser, the other one is an image of one candle only. You have already decided which copy will accompany the image. What should you do to help you decide on the right image to use?",
    "answers": [
      "Conduct an A/B test as part of the Instagram campaign in which you create two ads that are identical except for the image."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is correct about a positional model?",
    "answers": [
      "It gives more credit to first and last touch points whether they are clicks or impressions, while the credit for the remaining touchpoints in the middle is divided equally."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In A/B testing in advertising, it’s best practice to only change one variable at a time between the version A and B of your ad. Why is that?",
    "answers": [
      "When you only vary one variable and leave all other aspects of the different versions of the ad identical, then you will know exactly which variable was responsible for the difference in results"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? In statistical or math models you let the data speak and you don’t decide on a model ahead of time.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are working on a campaign with the objective to drive app downloads. You have created an audience on Facebook for your campaign. But, you also have a list of emails from people who have downloaded an app from you before, and you plan to create a custom audience using that list. Now, you would like to know which audience will be most likely to download your app. The new audience you created, or the custom audience of people who downloaded one of your apps before. Which study could help you?",
    "answers": ["You can run an A/B test"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Both A/B tests and Attribution Modeling studies help you to optimize your advertising, but how do they differ?",
    "answers": [
      "A/B tests help you to optimize within a campaign, whereas attribution modeling studies help you to optimize your budget across campaigns across platforms"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Historically, advertisers have relied on cookies to connect a sequence of touchpoints to a person.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },

  {
    "question": "What data might you include when presenting on conversion KPIs?",
    "answers": ["Charts and graphs on lead gen sign-ups and purchases"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How could you close your presentation?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some slides you'd want to include in your slide deck?",
    "answers": ["Goals, Objectives, and KPIs", "Lessons learned for the future"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a best practice to keep in mind when presenting data visually?",
    "answers": [
      "Get rid of excess information to make the slides uncluttered and clear",
      "Make sure your colors are deliberate, brand colors, or gradients of one color"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You're anticipating audience questions, especially one asking who the advertising went to, and where. You'd then include a slide addressing what?",
    "answers": ["How you set up your campaign"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How should you think about your movements during a presentation?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When creating a presentation, what's the main thing to keep in mind as you create it?",
    "answers": ["Who your audience is"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to talk about an experiment you ran that showed the path a customer took from your campaign to the result. Which of the following would you talk about?",
    "answers": ["Attribution study"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's the day of your presentation, and you are NOT freaking out. Why?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were presenting your data results, and wanted to talk about much you spent to get a new customer, what number would you include?",
    "answers": ["CAC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "DCB Cleaning ran an $800 campaign for businesses with new locations, offering one month of cleaning services for $300. They had 10 new clients sign up. What was the ROAS of the campaign?",
    "answers": ["3.75"]
  },
  {
    "question": "DCB Cleaning ran another campaign targeting big businesses looking to switch their cleaning services, offering a six month commitment for $1000. The campaign ran for three months, at $200 per month, and gained 6 new clients. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["10"]
  },
  {
    "question": "DCB Cleaning ran a campaign to get people to download their app, knowing that for every five downloads, they generate $200 in revenue. The campaign cost $1000 and they received 75 downloads. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko is launching a new product line on their website: bandanas for dogs. Each one costs $10, and in the month of their $800 campaign they sold out all 200 bandanas. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["2.5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Each bandana cost Inu + Neko $2 each to make. Remember that they sold 200 bandanas at $10 a piece and spent $800 on an ad campaign. What was their ROI on the campaign? (Round your answer to the nearest hundredth)",
    "answers": ["0.67"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Having spent $800 on their ad campaign, Inu + Neko sold out of their initial stock of 200 bandanas. They also collected 500 preorders. What is their ROAS now? Note: You do not need to take the cost of materials into account for the ROAS calculation.",
    "answers": ["8.75"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko ran another campaign driving traffic to their website, which cost them $1000 over the course of two months. They received 2,000 new website visits, each of whom averaged out to $5.50 a purchase. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["11"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla & Ivy ran a lead generation campaign for a free bouquet, knowing that one out of every four people eventually spend $50. They received 200 sign-ups for a campaign that cost $200. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["12.5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It costs Calla & Ivy $10 in materials to make each free bouquet. Keep in mind that they spent $200 on their marketing campaign and 50 of their 200 sign-ups each resulted in a $50 purchase. What is their ROI?",
    "answers": ["12.45"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla & Ivy ran a campaign to boost app downloads, knowing that one out of every six people eventually purchase a subscription for $100. They spent $800 on the campaign and received 48 downloads. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["1"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko has recently run a number of campaigns, and is calculating the Cost Per Result of each. First, they start with a reach campaign, which generated 1,000 impressions for a $200 campaign. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.20"]
  },
  {
    "question": "They ran another reach campaign spending the same amount ($200) and changed some of their settings. This time, they generated ten times more impressions than the last campaign, which generated 1,000 impressions. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.02"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Their next campaign was a lead generation campaign. They know that every five leads converts into a $20 sale. The campaign cost $800, and they generated 1,000 leads. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.80"]
  },
  {
    "question": "They ran another lead generation campaign, which cost them $200 per month for four months. Over that four months they brought in 2,000 leads, double the amount of leads as before. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.40"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Next, they ran a campaign to increase views on their grooming videos. They allocated a $10 daily budget for the month of September, which has 30 days. They received 75 plays by the end. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$4.00"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Not liking the Cost Per Result of the previous campaign, Inu + Neko ran another campaign and adjusted their settings in Ads Manager. They spent the same amount, $300, and received 300 views, which is four times the previous amount. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$1.00"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko is trying to drive more traffic to the new products on their site, and set up a conversion campaign, allotting $500 a month for six months. At the end of that time they made $20,000 in sales from 600 customers. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$5.00"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko wants to test out Catalogue Sales to showcase more inventory from their online store. They set up a campaign that cost $1500 total and lasted three months, and got 200 conversions for a total of $6000 revenue. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$7.50"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko set up a traffic campaign to drive visitors to their website, paying $200 a month for five months. Over the course of that time, they gained 10,000 new visits, half from advertising and half from organic. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.10"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After that campaign, they changed some of their settings, but set up the same five month campaign at the same price. After that time, they gained another 10,000 visitors, three-quarters of which came from organic traffic. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.40"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Calla & Ivy want to figure out the lifetime value of their customers. They know that the average customer's value is $50 a month, and the average lifespan of a customer is 5 years (60 months). What is the LTV?",
    "answers": ["$3000"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The information for Questions 2-5 will be connected. Each subsequent question will require information from the previous questions to solve. Calla & Ivy are now trying to figure out some of the components of lifetime value for a particular demographic that comes into the store to buy flowers. This demographic made 100 purchases and spent $12,000 in the last month. What is their Average Purchase Value?",
    "answers": ["$120"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Next, Calla & Ivy want to figure out the purchase frequency. There were 50 people in this demographic that made purchases last month. What is the Average Purchase Frequency Rate per month? You need to use the information in Question 2 to figure this one out.",
    "answers": ["2"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Average Customer Value per month for this particular demographic? You need to use the information in Questions 2 & 3 to figure this one out.",
    "answers": ["$240"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If the average lifespan of a customer is 5 years, what is the LTV per customer for this demographic? You need to use the answer from Question 4 to figure this one out.",
    "answers": ["$14,400"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The information in Questions 6-9 is all connected. Each subsequent question will require information from the previous questions to solve. Inu + Neko are now trying to calculate the LTV of their customers. Last month, they made $30,000 over 1500 purchases. What was their Average Purchase Value?",
    "answers": ["$20"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As for Inu + Neko's purchase frequency, they were able to see that 1000 people bought something at the store. What is the Average Purchase Frequency Rate per month? You need to use the information in Question 6 to figure this out.",
    "answers": ["1.5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Inu & Neko's Average Customer Value per month? You need to use the information from Questions 6 & 7 to figure this out.",
    "answers": ["$30"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If the average lifespan of a customer is 12 years (the lifetime of their pet), what is the LTV per customer? You need to use the answer from Question 8 to figure this out.",
    "answers": ["$4320"]
  },
  {
    "question": "SnackWall has increased the yearly subscription so that the Average Purchase Value has now changed to $2500 for small businesses. If there were 8 small businesses that each purchased one yearly subscription in the past year, and the Average Customer Lifespan is 10 years, what would the customer LTV for small businesses be?",
    "answers": ["$25,000"]
  },

  {
    "question": "What is the main reason for comparing a treatment group to a control group in an advertising experiment?",
    "answers": [
      "To measure the impact of the advertisement by comparing outcomes between exposed and unexposed groups"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is randomization important when designing a randomized controlled trial in advertising?",
    "answers": [
      "It helps ensure that the treatment and control groups are similar before the campaign begins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does an advertising experiment help you determine about a campaign?",
    "answers": ["Whether the campaign caused the results you observed"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is the intention-to-treat (ITT) approach used in advertising experiments?",
    "answers": [
      "It keeps participants in their assigned initial group to preserve randomization and reduce bias"
    ]
  },

  {
    "question": "What is considered a best practice when setting up an A/B test in Meta Ads Manager?",
    "answers": [
      "Test one variable at a time to accurately determine what caused the difference in results"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does a confidence level of 93% in an A/B test indicate?",
    "answers": [
      "There is a 93% chance that the winning version would win again if the test were repeated"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most effective next step after identifying a winning ad with a high confidence level?",
    "answers": [
      "Shift budget to the winning ad and continue testing for further optimization"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You're planning an ad campaign and want to use an A/B test to determine the best image. What is the most important principle to follow when setting up your test?",
    "answers": ["Vary only one element between version A and B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra wants to compare two versions of her Facebook ad that feature different images. She’s using Meta Ads Manager. Which step should she take first to begin the A/B test?",
    "answers": ["Turn on the A/B test toggle when setting up the campaign"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following outlines the key components of an effective campaign presentation?",
    "answers": ["Goals, key data, insights and recommended actions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most effective way to use storytelling in your campaign presentation?",
    "answers": ["Connect goals to actions, results and future recommendations"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is it essential to include both results and insights in a campaign presentation?",
    "answers": [
      "Results show performance, while insights explain what the results mean and what to do next"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of data visualization in campaign presentations?",
    "answers": [
      "To clearly communicate key results and trends in an easily understandable format"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "As a business owner, you’d like to set up a presence on a text-based social media platform where you can engage with real-time updates, follow niche interests, and provide real-time customer service on a personal level. Which of the following would be an ideal platform?",
    "answers": ["Twitter"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Meta shares its targeted advertising software and data corpus with which of the following two platforms, in addition to Facebook, which it owns? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": ["Instagram", "WhatsApp"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Twitter is one of the only social media platforms that has the same unified profile for individuals and brands alike.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You created a dance sequence and want to share your moves and encourage others to participate in a hashtag challenge such as #DiscoDanceChallenge. Which of the following would be an ideal platform?",
    "answers": ["TikTok"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following can you do on Messenger? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Create group chats",
      "Share photos and videos",
      "Play games with friends"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Businesses can use stickers on Instagram stories to encourage viewers to engage directly with the business.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As a business owner, you’d like to set up a presence on a social media platform where you can network with others in your industry, post news and accomplishments and find potential team members to fill open roles. Which of the following would be an ideal platform?",
    "answers": ["Linkedin"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which major social media platform has the same unified profile for individuals and brands alike?",
    "answers": ["Twitter"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: You have to have an account to get started using TikTok.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You recently finished making a new batch of affordable earrings and want to promote your brand and products. Your target audience is teenagers from ages 13-17. On which platform should you make an account?",
    "answers": ["Instagram"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a free messaging app you can use to message your friends and family using internet connection while avoiding SMS fees or charges?",
    "answers": ["WhatsApp"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Youtube is a platform designed for sharing video content.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "At its core marketing involves which of these steps? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Creating messages related to or promoting the product",
      "Understanding and studying the audience or customers for a product"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are types of digital marketing? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Content marketing",
      "Display advertising",
      "Email marketing",
      "Social media marketing",
      "Search engine optimization",
      "Display advertising"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false: In 2014, Meta acquired the photo-sharing platform Instagram.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "For which of the following reasons do companies use social media?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about Social Media Marketing? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Its focus is to connect people and provide people the ability to share and create content",
      "It is a type of digital marketing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are part of the SMART goal framework? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": ["Time-bound", "Achievable", "Specific"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a KPI for the following SMART goal? “Get 10,000 website visits during the month of May”.",
    "answers": ["number of monthly website visits"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the 5-letter framework through which you should plan your business goals?",
    "answers": ["SMART"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of Key Performance Indicators [KPIs]? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "A measurement of website traffic to your new product page",
      "The number of subscriptions/sales",
      "Your conversion rate for purchases"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maria set a SMART goal for her chocolate business: “Decrease the use of paid ads to market older products and reduce marketing spending by 30% by the end of 6 months”. What would be a good KPI for her to use when evaluating if she is reaching this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "Cost per sale (how much it cost in marketing dollars to generate a sale)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla and Ivy set a SMART goal for their B2C flower business: “Direct 20% more customers to the website through social media posts in the next three months”. What would a good KPI for Calla and Ivy to evaluate to see if they are reaching their goal?",
    "answers": ["Website traffic"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Devon set a SMART goal for his hand-knit sweater business: “Optimize social media ads to gain 5% more customer contacts at a more efficient rate than the previous month”. What would be a good KPI for him to use when evaluating if he is reaching this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "Cost per lead (how much it cost in marketing dollars to generate a lead)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When outlining your target audience, you should consider all of the following except:",
    "answers": ["Your target audience’s eating habits"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Harry was recently promoted at work and wanted to buy himself something to celebrate. He sees a suit in a magazine ad and really wants to buy it. In which stage of the customer journey is Harry?",
    "answers": ["Desire"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: The process of moving people through the customer journey results in what marketers refer to as a marketing funnel.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The audience that will typically get most of your attention since you expect them to become your most valuable group of customers is:",
    "answers": ["Primary target audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following research tools lets you track the keywords your followers are searching for, their online posting behavior, and the devices they use?",
    "answers": ["Twitter Business Analytics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Demographic information such as age, geographic location, and prior purchasing history is a key factor to consider when determining your target audience.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are stages in the typical customer journey? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Advocacy", "Awareness", "Conversion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Things you should consider when outlining your target audience include which of the following? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Your target audience’s needs",
      "Your target audience’s interests",
      "Key demographic data that describes your target audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Envy is a stage in the typical customer journey.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re looking to do mainly B2B (business to business) marketing and to post job applications. Your go-to social media platform should be:",
    "answers": ["LinkedIn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re looking to build a community online. Your go-to social media platform should be:",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good general guidelines for a corporate blog? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Blog posts must respect copyright, privacy, fair use, financial disclosure, and other applicable laws",
      "Blog posts should not disclose any information that is confidential or proprietary to the company"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the three core values that a social media policy should achieve, which category does the following statement fit in? “Nordstrom makes it clear that employees can be held legally responsible for what they post, so they should make sure that they stay within the company guidelines. “",
    "answers": [
      "A social media policy must guard against legal risks to the organization"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following a quality of a website or a blog? The content is not interactive",
    "answers": ["Website"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which benefit of blogging is the following an example of? Your blog content is shared on social media platforms such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram, and Twitter.",
    "answers": ["Expand your content’s reach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re looking to reach the largest possible audience with the most precise targeted advertising tools. Your go-to social media platform should be:",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the three core values that a social media policy should achieve, which category does the following statement fit in? “Nordstrom referred to company guidelines that can help employees to represent the company in a way that doesn’t harm the brand”",
    "answers": ["A social media policy must protect the brand"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following a quality of a website or a blog? The writing is often more informal",
    "answers": ["Blog"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which benefit of blogging is the following an example of? Posting valuable content consistently helps elevate a company as a trusted resource within their industry leading to more visitors, more potential customers and more sales.",
    "answers": ["Build credibility"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of your LinkedIn profile should be your virtual elevator pitch?",
    "answers": ["Summary"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Determine whether the following statement is true or false: Now more than ever, brands must engage with the customers through social media.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a soft skill?",
    "answers": ["Leadership"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these things are NOT essential for your company social media page?",
    "answers": ["Your CEO’s biography"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following components of the EPIC framework does the following statement encompass? How that business got started, and why the world should pay attention",
    "answers": ["Existence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a part of a brand’s purpose?",
    "answers": ["The brand’s logo"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which voice would be most fitting to connect with the following audience? Teenagers between the ages of ten to thirteen, looking to buy colorful jewelry",
    "answers": ["friendly and casual"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a part of brand identity?",
    "answers": ["The company’s origin story"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which voice would be most fitting to connect with the following audience? College students looking for humorous critique on current events and media",
    "answers": ["witty and smart"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you’re a visually oriented business, what major social media platform is essential for your business to have a page on?",
    "answers": ["Instagram"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The benefits of cultivating brand loyalty include which of the following? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Become an identity they can relate to",
      "Make customers feel good about consuming your product"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What should your branding do for customers? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Customers will follow your brand to new products",
      "Customers become less price-sensitive if they’re loyal to your brand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the essential components of your social media marketing pages? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": ["A profile picture", "A brief brand bio"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following components of the EPIC framework does the following statement encompass? What the business does and why they do it, including articulating a set of values for the business",
    "answers": ["Purpose"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the first major social media platform you should set up a company page for?",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A good way to get people to share Facebook posts you create is to: (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Present a problem and offer a solution", "@ mention them "]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? You should always shoot your videos in horizontal landscape view to make them seem more cinematic.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re drafting the text for a Facebook advertisement. What’s a good thing to add to guarantee greater engagement?",
    "answers": ["Include an image in your post"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the best performing type of post on Facebook?",
    "answers": ["Video"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The social media feature—used across Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, and more— that lets you tag your post with a category and make it more findable is called a:",
    "answers": ["hashtag"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you tag another person or social media user with an @ preceding their name in a post, that’s called a:",
    "answers": ["mention"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? You can safely assume that people viewing your video advertisement will hear the accompanying audio.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were a food delivery service trying to interact with your customers on social media, what would be the best course of action?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask your customers on your stories: “What did you cook this weekend?!”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Instagram users can maximize engagement through use of: (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Topically appropriate hashtags",
      "Strategic use of the multiple photo option",
      "@ mentions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Some of the key elements that make up a social media post are:",
    "answers": [
      "Images or video",
      "Hashtags or @mentions",
      "Call-to-actions & links"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not true about hashtags?",
    "answers": ["The more there are, the better"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which social media platform has the shortest post “lifetime”?",
    "answers": ["Twitter"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Moderators for a Facebook Page can respond to page comments and send messages from the page, as well as post directly to the page.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following can be considered organic content? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Calla and Ivy share their “customer of the week” in a tweet",
      "A behind the scenes video of the pets at Inu & Neko on Tiktok"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Using Hashtags in your post are a great way to connect with potential customers.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Within how many days should a brand respond to social media comments?",
    "answers": ["1"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are some benefits of storyboarding? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Shows your team what you are creating",
      "Helps to visualize content",
      "Creates more polished, professional content"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You run a camera-rental company and Marge posts on your Linkedin page that her rented DSLR camera had a cracked lens. Her comment reads: “I went on vacation with my husband and all our anniversary photos have a big crack! Your camera is tearing us apart!” How do you respond?",
    "answers": [
      "“Hey Marge—we’re sorry to hear that. That’s not in line with our standards, and we’ll DM you now to talk about this and give you a free rental as well.”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is one of the three main categories of engaging social media content?",
    "answers": ["Educational posts"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which social media scheduler has a built-in chatbot creator?",
    "answers": ["Sprout Social"]
  },
  {
    "question": "DCB Cleaners receives an accusation of shoddy construction from James on their Facebook page. It reads: “My DCB snack bar fell down! Screw you!” How do you respond?",
    "answers": [
      "“Hey James—we’re sorry to hear that. That’s not in line with our standards, and we’ll DM you now to talk about this and send someone your way as soon as possible to fix it.”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra noticed a jump in new followers on Instagram on May 10. What could be a reasonable cause of that?",
    "answers": ["The Insta Live at the Festival on May 9 had many impressions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla & Ivy is going to be hosting some summer classes on floral arrangement. What are some ways that Imra can encourage customers to engage with the promotion posts for the classes? Choose two.",
    "answers": [
      "Include a video.",
      "Include all the information, such as class titles, descriptions, and dates."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Since Calla & Ivy is a small business, and loves to support and work with the small businesses in the city, Imra has started featuring businesses in the neighborhood and how Calla & Ivy works with them through her Local Business Feature posts. What could be the reason for the high impression rate?",
    "answers": ["The posts are being shared many times"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Considering that Calla & Ivy’s audience is on Instagram during the early- to mid-afternoon, how is Imra doing on her posting schedule?",
    "answers": [
      "Pretty good! Most posts are between that time, but Calla & Ivy is still seeing good engagement from posts outside of the time frame."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a social media platform that Calla & Ivy hasn’t used yet and should expand?",
    "answers": ["Pinterest"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Please be sure to expand the \"Instructions\" tab shown above to access the content calendar needed to answer each question. Take a look at Imra’s blog post promotions. Which post had the least readership on the website, and what insight would that give her for writing future blog posts? (Choose one)",
    "answers": [
      "Seasonal flowers post had the least engagement; observe the qualities of posts that do well and edit your seasonal flower posts going forward."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra wanted to broadcast the local Tulip Fest, on May 2, 3, and 9, to her followers in the hopes that it would boost engagement. She chose to use Insta Live video to show her audience the festival as it was happening. What could be a lesson to take into future posts?",
    "answers": ["Remind followers about the live video before it happens"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra has started sharing articles to Twitter she thinks her audience may find useful. What is something that Imra should keep in mind when reposting articles written by other people?",
    "answers": [
      "Imra should remember to mention (@) the account or publication where she found the articles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra makes a note of the important holidays throughout the month of May which might prompt her customers to purchase her flowers. For each holiday, she has planned a post for Facebook with a link to her website and a purchase page. Which holiday post was most successful with engagement?",
    "answers": ["Mother’s Day"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Considering that Calla & Ivy’s audience is on Twitter during the late afternoon and evening, how is Imra doing on her posting schedule?",
    "answers": [
      "She is doing okay. Imra needs to adjust some of her posting times."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra has started posting about the bouquet creations she makes for her clients, in order to showcase the flowers and her skills, which will hopefully draw more people to order something they haven’t seen before. During what time of day are the bouquet creations posts most successful?",
    "answers": ["It does not matter what time they are posted"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra has started a Flower of the Week post on Twitter, to help educate her followers about the different types of flowers out in the world. Is Twitter the best platform for this type of post?",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re creating an ad for a boutique smartphone case company called Case. Your target audience is design-conscious people aged 21-39 with an interest in modern art and minimalist home decor. Your ad creative is a photo of four well-dressed 20s-somethings laughing over coffee, with their Case-covered phones placed on the table. Your copy reads: “These Cases are like War Bonds—An Investment That’ll Last Forever!” Your CTA says “Shop Now!” Which part of the ad is ineffective?",
    "answers": ["Copy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brady is looking to advertise a new job opening at his company and is not having much luck on traditional job posting sites. To expedite the process and better target ideal candidates, he decides to run an ad. Which of the following ad types would best suit his advertising needs?",
    "answers": ["Sponsored InMail ads on LinkedIn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? A post is “organic” when it is posted from your account and spreads from people who engage with your content to their friends without having to pay.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are ways that you can advertise on Twitter? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Sponsor a trending hashtag",
      "A traditional “in-feed” ad",
      "Promote your Twitter account"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A video that conveys your message and tells a story is referred to as which component of a social media ad?",
    "answers": ["Creative"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re creating an ad for a boutique smartphone case company called Case. The target audience is design-conscious people aged 21-39, with an interest in modern art and minimalist home decor. Your ad creative is a video of four well-dressed 20s-somethings laughing over coffee, with their Case-covered phones placed on the table. Your copy reads: “You’re stylish—shouldn’t your phone be, too?” Your CTA says “Book Now” Which part of the ad is ineffective?",
    "answers": ["CTA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Image ads are some of the most common ads that appear on social media, incorporating an eye-catching photo, overlaid with little-to-no text on the image itself.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If you’re advertising on a platform like Pinterest that doesn’t offer Call-to-Action buttons, you can’t include a CTA in your ad.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "While scrolling on your Instagram feed, you encounter what looks to be a sponsored post for a skincare product on a beauty influencer’s page. Which required details of the post let you know that it’s sponsored? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "There’s a “sponsored” label that lets you know the post is sponsored",
      "The post has a call to action button"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are ad formats offered to users for purchase on Youtube? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Video ad", "Overlay ad", "Display ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The age, gender, location, and interests of your customers make up which component of a social media ad?",
    "answers": ["Target Audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re running ads for a business that designs tailor-made dresses and operates primarily through consultations. Which of the following Facebook Call to Action buttons should you use if you want people to sign up for a consultation?",
    "answers": ["Book Now"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are noticing that the number of people who view your Facebook posts is declining. What would be a good course of action to entice new viewers to your page?",
    "answers": ["Invest in paid advertising on Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A concise statement of what you want to accomplish in your target market is which part of a creative brief?",
    "answers": ["Objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You decide to run an ad campaign and create an objective to increase conversions on your website. Which KPI would accurately measure this objective? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Number of purchases", "ROAS"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An ad agency submits a creative brief to you. It looks almost complete, but it’s missing the single most important benefit of your offer for your target audience. Which creative brief element is missing?",
    "answers": ["Key benefit"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of your creative brief describes what you’re trying to promote or sell?",
    "answers": ["Offer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Freelancers who commit to a certain amount of work and payment on a monthly basis are paid a:",
    "answers": ["Retainer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’re writing a creative brief and need to cover other companies in your field that target your same target audience. Which of the following items should you include information about in your creative brief?",
    "answers": ["Competitors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: When shooting a video for your ad campaign, always shoot vertically.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Wes is the owner of a spa and massage center called OASIS. He wants to convey to potential customers the mental and physical benefits of his massage and spa offerings, as well as the accessibility of his business. Which of the following tips should he follow to appropriately get his message across? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Use customer reviews to support claims about physical and mental health benefits",
      "Mention price or special offers for spa treatments and massages"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An ad agency submits a creative brief to you. It looks almost complete, but it’s missing a project timeline, deadlines, a budget, and who will approve the final work. Which creative brief element is missing?",
    "answers": ["Logistics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You need someone to produce all the written materials that represent a brand. You’re looking to hire a:",
    "answers": ["Copywriter"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good tips to keep in mind when shooting a picture for your ad campaign? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Follow the Rule of Thirds",
      "Keep it simple",
      "Use attractive color combinations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lisa is writing copy for an ad she plans to run on Facebook to promote her stationery shop. She’s beginning to organize her copy, starting with creating an interesting and engaging opening to draw new customers in. What should she look to accomplish in the opening? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "She should call out her audience",
      "She should pique the curiosity of her audience with feelings or logic",
      "She addresses a pain point felt by her audience regarding cheap or cookie cutter greeting cards and stationery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Any business that collects and controls the personal information of California residents should comply with the CCPA.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the acronym for the US law that took effect in 2000 and limits the collection and use of personal information of people under the age of 13?",
    "answers": ["COPPA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A website-specific code stored in a person’s browser to ease navigation is called what?",
    "answers": ["Cookie"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are GDPR data protection obligations for companies who collect data? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Companies are prohibited from collecting certain data categories (like ethnicity or sexual orientation)",
      "Companies must designate people whose job it is to protect the data they receive",
      "Companies must alert people within 72 hours if their personal data was leaked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the maximum fine related to GDPR violations?",
    "answers": ["4% of the annual revenue of a company"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The main goal of industry self-regulatory organizations is to enforce data protection laws.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are NOT European self-regulatory principles for Data-Driven Advertising?",
    "answers": ["Full transparency"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How is data-driven advertising different from other forms of advertising?",
    "answers": [
      "Ads are matched with the audience who sees them, regardless of where the ad appears"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Facebook users can choose to opt out of seeing ads from specific advertisers on Facebook.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The GDPR is an international agreement that applies to both companies in the United States and the European Union, independent of where their customers or users are based.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The DAA’s YourAdChoices program performs the same role in the US that the GDPR does in the European Union.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Ideally, the cookie would function as the memory of the interactions between a website and a person. However, a person may use different computers, different browsers and mobile devices, and cookies don’t work across devices.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you’re advertising on Instagram for the life insurance division of a major company. You want your ads to be seen by people in the American Northeast over the age 50. Which advertising targeting option should you use?",
    "answers": ["Create Your Own Audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? After creating an ad, you submit it for review to make sure that it meets Instagram’s Advertising Policies.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Facebook campaign objective should be selected to generate sales on a website or app?",
    "answers": ["Conversions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What action would a business want its customers to take if it selects “Promote Your Page” as its campaign objective when creating an ad on Facebook?",
    "answers": ["Like their page"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? A good Instagram Story ad typically consists of one long scene rather than multiple short scenes.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You just opened a thrift store in your town and are looking to utilize your Facebook Business page to reach people around your brick-and-mortar business. Which Facebook Ads Manager objective should you choose?",
    "answers": ["Promote Your Business Locally"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Once you've set a specific goal for your business that you'd like your Facebook ad to help you achieve, the next step is to choose the promotion or ad objective that matches your business goal.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you have a surfboard business that you’re promoting an Instagram post for. Most of your work is custom, so you need to talk with customers before they order. Your promoted post should direct them towards:",
    "answers": ["Your Direct Messages"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Engagement rates are higher for Instagram stories without sound, as people frequently watch them muted.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you own a sporting goods store. You decide to boost a pre-existing post as an ad to create more awareness around your business and increase online visibility for your business. Which success metric should you track to determine whether your ad was successful?",
    "answers": ["Post engagement number"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of ad placement options for ads created on Ads Manager? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Feed", "In-Stream", "Search"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the Meta total value ad auction equation tells you how much an advertiser is willing to pay to achieve their desired outcome?",
    "answers": ["Advertiser Bid"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say two skateboard companies are competing in an auction to show one person, named Daniel, an ad. Daniel lives in the mountains and loves hiking, snowboarding, and skateboarding. Company One targeted people who like skateboarding who live near the mountains in a few U.S. states. Company Two is targeting all men who like to skateboard in the U.S. Company Two budgeted way more money than Company One for ads. Which part of their Total Value score will this boost?",
    "answers": ["Advertiser Bid"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following ad account sections is it necessary for you to fill in for legal reasons, as there may be restrictions on certain types of advertising in your region?",
    "answers": ["Business Information and Advertising Purpose"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following shows the correct order of actions you need to take at the ad level?",
    "answers": [
      "Choose format → add photos and videos → write copy → define destination"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the third step in the campaign-creation process in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": [
      "Create your ads—choose the ad format and then add videos or photos, write copy, and define your destination"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what Ads Manager business tool category would you find tools to learn more about why Meta might have rejected your ad?",
    "answers": ["Manage Business"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the Meta total value ad auction equation tells you the numerical score Meta assigns to an ad through the auction?",
    "answers": ["Total Value"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? If you have a Facebook profile or an Instagram account, you automatically also have an Ads Manager account.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? When you change your currency or time zone, you will NOT create a new ad account—instead, your current account will be altered.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ad campaign objective group (and customer journey stage) includes objectives that get people to consider, seek information about, and engage with your product or service?",
    "answers": ["Consideration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new mattress company is trying to introduce itself to customers that are likely to be interested in and remember them. Which objective should the nonprofit apply?",
    "answers": ["Awareness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of budget tells Facebook how much you’re willing to spend over the entire runtime of your campaign?",
    "answers": ["Lifetime budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you have an expected revenue of $100,000. With the Rule of Thirds in mind, what should your upper limit for advertising spending be in dollars?",
    "answers": ["33,333"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which bid strategy allows you to set the average amount you’re willing to pay for a desired outcome, like a conversion on your website?",
    "answers": ["Cost per Result Goal"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which bid strategy is best for making sure you don’t sell any single item ever at a loss?",
    "answers": ["Bid Cap"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you’re doing a split-test, which variable should you change if you want to see whether one image-text combination gets more leads than another?",
    "answers": ["Creative"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new mattress company is trying to introduce itself to customers that are likely to be interested in and remember them. Which objective should the company apply?",
    "answers": ["Awareness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Meta ad campaign objective group (and customer journey stage) includes objectives to create initial awareness of your brand?",
    "answers": ["Awareness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say you’re trying to achieve a marketing goal for app downloads. You want 40,000 people to download the app, which costs $1 per download. You make $0.50 in profits per download. What’s the maximum amount in dollars you can spend on advertising without losing money?",
    "answers": ["20,000"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which bid strategy tells Meta to bid with the goal of getting you the lowest possible cost per desired action, while also spending your entire budget by the end of the campaign?",
    "answers": ["Highest Volume"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which variable in a split compares how your ad performs with a video asset versus an image carousel, or with any other differentiation in ad-level adjustments?",
    "answers": ["Creative"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The three audience types you can create in Ads Manager are Core Audiences, Lookalike Audiences, and _____________?",
    "answers": ["Custom Audiences"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A music shop wants to start advertising to bring more people in for in-person instrument lessons. They have a big following on Facebook, and a lot of people like, comment on, and share their mini video lessons. They know they can capitalize on that audience somehow, but they’re not sure how. What would you tell them?",
    "answers": [
      "Create a Custom Audience from viewers of the videos, and target them with advertising for in-person lessons"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: You must have a Lifetime budget selected in order to set a specific ads schedule (i.e. one with specified days and times).",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You've selected \"traffic\" as your campaign objective in Ads Manager to drive relevant people to your website. What ad delivery optimization option is available for this campaign objective at the ad set level?",
    "answers": [
      "Maximize landing page views to target users who are likely to click the link and load the page"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "As you’re setting up your Ad Set options, like audience, placement, and budget, why should you pay attention to the Audience Size dial and the Estimated Daily Results measure?",
    "answers": [
      "It will measure in real time an estimated audience size so you can tell if you’re setting options that are making it too small or leaving it too big."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An apparel company known for its line of t-shirts and hoodies is trying to boost an accessories line it launched last year, but they can't seem to get it to pick up. They know they have sales, and they know they have visitors to the product page, but they can't connect the two, and retargeting their core audience doesn't seem to be working. They recently installed the Meta Pixel on the website. What are all the events they can now track?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A skate park just opened in a suburban town, the biggest of its kind in the Northeast USA. You're creating a Core Audience for them. What criteria would you probably choose?",
    "answers": [
      "Location: Northeast USA Age: 18-25 Gender: All Detailed Targeting: Skateboarding, Spots, Extreme Sports, Vans, Thrasher Magazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The three audience types you can create in Ads Manager are Core Audiences, Custom Audiences, and _____________?",
    "answers": ["Lookalike Audiences"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A skate park just opened in a suburban town, the biggest of its kind in the Northeast USA: You're creating a Core Audience for them. What criteria would you probably choose?",
    "answers": [
      "Location: Northeast USA Age: 18-25 Gender: All Detailed Targeting: Skateboarding, Spots, Extreme Sports, Vans, Thrasher Magazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ad format opens up a broader catalog of up to 50 different products when tapped on?",
    "answers": ["Collection"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A men's retail business is launching a new shoe line with eight different style/color combinations. All styles must be shown to the audience. However, the business doesn't know which new products will best sell. The business wants to link each style page directly to the product to receive pixel information. Which ad format should the retailer use to meet these requirements?",
    "answers": ["Carousel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? When creating image-based ads, you should crop them to make sure they look great in a square, vertical, and horizontal format.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which KPI measures all reactions, comments, shares and clicks on your post?",
    "answers": ["Post Engagements"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A beard oil company is new to Ads Manager and wants to begin experimenting and creating ads. Which ad format is the best one with which to start?",
    "answers": ["Single image"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser is delivering an ad campaign and recently created an Instagram business profile. Where should the advertiser navigate in Ads Manager in order to include the Instagram business profile in the campaign?",
    "answers": ["Ad level"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new alcoholic seltzer company wants to compete in a crowded market by creating a video ad campaign which people will remember when they go to the store. Which metric should the company use to evaluate the success of the campaign?",
    "answers": ["Estimated Ad Recall Lift"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which KPI measures how many times an ad’s link to reach your website was clicked?",
    "answers": ["Link Clicks"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What feature is unique to Instagram Stories and Facebook Stories?",
    "answers": ["Content disappears after 24 hours"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What can a boosted post help an advertiser achieve?",
    "answers": ["Increase engagement on Page content"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Facebook roles are able to manage an ad account? (Choose two)",
    "answers": ["Administrator", "Advertiser"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the structure of an Ad Campaign, as set through Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Campaign --> ad set --> ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to set a maximum bid amount for individual actions like link clicks and landing page views. What should you create?",
    "answers": ["Facebook ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main difference between the Traffic and Sales objectives?",
    "answers": [
      "The Traffic objective optimizes for clicks, while the Sales objective optimizes for actions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What action does a business want its customers to take if it selects Traffic as its campaign objective?",
    "answers": ["Visit business website"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You recently installed the Meta Pixel on your company’s website. At what level should you choose the conversion event optimization?",
    "answers": ["Ad set"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two variables are available for A/B tests? (Choose two)",
    "answers": ["Placement", "Audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two settings can be changed at the ad set level? (Choose two)",
    "answers": ["Bid amount", "Placements"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the total value ad auction equation covers feedback from people that view or hide your ad, as well as findings of “low-quality” attributes such as sensationalized language, engagement bait, and more?",
    "answers": ["Ad Quality"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A retailer is opening a new store and wants to optimize towards generating more physical store visits by creating strong awareness in the local population. Which objective should the retailer apply?",
    "answers": ["Awareness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand wants to send more people to the App Store to download its app. Which campaign objective is most relevant?",
    "answers": ["App Promotion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are GDPR citizen rights? (Select three)",
    "answers": [
      "Citizens have the right to access the personal information received about them",
      "Citizens have the right to correct their information",
      "Citizens have the right to have all the information that was collected and saved about them erased"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of major ad placement places your ads before, during or after video content?",
    "answers": ["In-Stream"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to forecast the reach of their ad set. Which tool should an advertiser use to perform this task?",
    "answers": ["Estimated daily results"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which major section of Ads Manager (found in the top navigation bar) would you prepare mockup ad campaigns?",
    "answers": ["Advertise"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are GDPR data protection obligations for companies who collect data? (Select three)",
    "answers": [
      "Companies are prohibited from collecting certain data categories (like ethnicity or sexual orientation)",
      "Companies must alert people within 72 hours if their personal data was leaked",
      "Companies must designate people whose job it is to protect the data they receive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An online store wants to build a database of customer information but it does not have the Meta Pixel installed. Which campaign objective meets this business goal?",
    "answers": ["Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the pixel installed?",
    "answers": ["Business website"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If your goal is to generate sales on your website, which campaign objective should you select?",
    "answers": ["Sales"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What must you do first in order to establish a business presence on Instagram?",
    "answers": ["Switch a personal profile to a business profile"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand launches a new website and wants to encourage people to visit it. What should the brand select first to create the campaign?",
    "answers": ["The appropriate campaign objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two benefits of selecting Advantage+ Placements?",
    "answers": [
      "It reaches more people across Meta apps and technologies",
      "It gives the ad delivery systems increased flexibility to find the best results"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business only has high-quality photos as creative assets. It's interested in testing video ads but doesn't have resources to create them. What solution should the business try?",
    "answers": ["Slideshow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which interface can be used to set up a Facebook ad campaign?",
    "answers": ["Ads Manager"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is an ad account permission granted to the analyst role?",
    "answers": ["Access reports"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business decides to close its store early during the holidays and wants to make sure its customers are made aware organically. What should the business create?",
    "answers": ["A Page post"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the total value ad auction equation tells you how much an advertiser is willing to pay to achieve their desired outcome?",
    "answers": ["Advertiser Bid"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A bank releases a mobile banking app and wants to increase app downloads with its new customers. Which campaign objective should the bank use?",
    "answers": ["App Promotion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In order to access the ad scheduling feature in Ads Manager, which setting must you select?",
    "answers": ["Lifetime budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What can you estimate when creating a Awareness campaign?",
    "answers": ["Reach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which major section of Ads Manager (found in the top navigation bar) could you learn more about why Meta might have rejected your ad?",
    "answers": ["Manage Business"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new ecommerce company wants more people to start conversations through Messenger or WhatsApp for customer service. Which campaign objective should be used to meet this business goal?",
    "answers": ["Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business set up an awareness campaign, a consideration campaign, and a conversion campaign to get new customers to their first purchase. If they spent $10,000 total and got 500 new customers, what was their Customer Acquisition Cost?",
    "answers": ["$20 per customer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company sells products that cost them $5 each to produce. They recently spent $2500 on advertising, and sold 300 of them at a $20 price point. What was their ROI?",
    "answers": ["0.5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing manager is attempting to collect data on their campaign. Where would they gather metrics from?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business recently ran a consideration campaign, where they spent $1000 total for two months. At the end of that time they had 10,000 new visitors to their website. What was their Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.10"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to see how well its campaigns are going. They've had an ROAS of around 3 in the past, and want to get a bigger return than that. They spent $600 and sold $2,100 worth. How did they do?",
    "answers": ["Better — their ROAS went up by .5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to evaluate how much they're spending on their customers, versus how much their customers go on to spend. If they want to see how much they spent on getting the customer to a first purchase, that measurement would be:",
    "answers": ["CAC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business recently ran a campaign where their ROI was 3. They ran a second campaign where their ROAS was 4. Did they do better on the second campaign?",
    "answers": ["We can't tell, since ROI and ROAS are different measurements"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to evaluate their campaign, and specifically wants to look at how much they spent for a customer to take an action. This measurement would be:",
    "answers": ["CPR"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business is setting up a campaign, and is thinking ahead to which metrics they would want to track. Which KPIs would you track for a conversion campaign?",
    "answers": ["Purchases, store visits, or lead generation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local car dealership's average customer comes in once every 10 years, and spends $30,000 on each purchase. An average customer in that particular town will spend 40 years frequenting that dealer. What is their lifetime value?",
    "answers": ["$120,000"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business recently ran an awareness campaign, where they spent $200 a month for three months. At the end of that time they gained 2000 impressions. What was their Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.30"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business ran a consideration campaign, where their Cost Per Result was $0.50. Considering their previous campaign returned a Cost Per Result of $0.75, how did they do?",
    "answers": ["Better — their Cost Per Result went down"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company recently sold $10,000 worth of products, yet only spent $2000 on their advertising. What was their ROI, if they sold 5000 units, which cost $.50 to make?",
    "answers": ["5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A coffee shop's average customer comes in twice a week, and spends $5 on each purchase. An average customer will spend five years frequenting that coffee shop. What is their lifetime value?",
    "answers": ["$2,600"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you work in the marketing department of a large electronics company. You are planning to set up a new conversion campaign on Facebook focused on generating online sales for computer monitors. Your manager asks you to make sure you can report on the effectiveness of your campaign once the campaign is completed. How do you make sure you can fulfill her requirements?",
    "answers": [
      "By setting up a Holdout Test before the campaign starts running"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you run an online art supply store. You are looking to increase awareness of online purchases by 5 percentage points among the target audience within three months. Which test would best measure this goal?",
    "answers": ["Brand Survey Test"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are elements of an experimental design?",
    "answers": ["Treatment Group", "Control Group", "Treatment Variable"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is it important to randomly assign people to the control or the treatment group in an experiment?",
    "answers": [
      "It helps to minimize the effect of external variables outside of your control on the results"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do we mean by ‘control group’ in an experiment?",
    "answers": ["The group that won’t be exposed to the treatment"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you want to track customer actions taken on your company’s app. Which Meta tool would be most helpful?",
    "answers": ["The Meta SDK"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does it mean when Meta says it uses Intention to Treat (ITT) in advertising effectiveness tests?",
    "answers": [
      "It means that people who are part of the test (or treatment) group in an experiment will remain in that group, even if they ended up not seeing the ad that was intended for them in the test"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the difference between a Holdout Test and a Brand Survey Test on Meta?",
    "answers": [
      "A Holdout Test measures the effect of your ads on conversions, whereas a Brand Survey Test measures the effect of your ads on ad recall and other brand related metrics measured through the use of a survey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You run the marketing for a high end clothing retailer and recently ran a holdout test for your company’s Facebook ad campaigns. In Meta Ads Manager, you look at your overview and observe how many additional conversions happened as a result of your ad. This is called the:",
    "answers": ["Conversion Lift"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an acceptable confidence level for your test?",
    "answers": ["90% and above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to run an experiment for your company’s advertising campaign. When designing your experiment, you randomly assign people to a control group and a treatment group. Studies that use this type of experiment are referred to as:",
    "answers": ["Randomized Control Trials (RCTs)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When Meta says it uses Intention to Treat (ITT) in advertising effectiveness tests, it means that those who are part of the test (or treatment) group in an experiment will not remain in the group.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you use an experiment to test the effectiveness of your advertising campaign, what do we mean when we refer to the treatment or test group?",
    "answers": ["The group of people that definitely saw your ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The core of your Brand Survey Test is:",
    "answers": ["Creating your poll questions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false: A Holdout Test uses a test and a control group and a Brand Survey test does not.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you ran a Brand Survey test for your campaign on Facebook and it is clear from the report that the confidence level for your test is low. In fact, it says in your report: “the chance that your Facebook ads caused brand lift of 63.2%”. You would like to see a higher confidence level. What could you do?",
    "answers": [
      "Keep running the campaign and increase the test period and the ad budget"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you work in the marketing department of a large clothing retailer. You want to run a marketing mix modeling study. Which of the following statements regarding the benefits of conducting this study are true? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "It can help plan how to best spend your money next year to improve results.",
      "It can help you analyze last year’s data to understand what worked.",
      "It can predict what will work in the future for your company."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When you are only testing two variations of one variable, you use an A/B test to determine which version will produce the best results.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is correct about a time decay attribution model?",
    "answers": [
      "It gives credit to touchpoints (clicks or impressions) based on how recently they happened."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Statistical models are not as robust as rule based models and less accurately reflect reality.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When we want to track advertising effectiveness across the whole customer journey, we do not need to be able to monitor behavior on the different platforms.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a component of the attribution method?",
    "answers": ["Marketing channels"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you work in the marketing department of a large clothing retailer. You are working on a ‘year in review’ presentation and you would like to show how your advertising on different platforms (TV, radio, Facebook and Youtube) contributed to sales for the denim line you introduced this year. You step to a market research agency to help you with this. What type of study should they do for you?",
    "answers": ["They should run a marketing mix modeling study"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is correct about a last click attribution model?",
    "answers": [
      "It gives all the credit for a conversion to the last ad a user clicked on before converting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Attribution is mostly used to evaluate the impact of online media channels on a purchase.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you are planning a campaign for a shoe brand on Instagram. You have several images of the shoes you want to promote, but you are not sure which image will work best. After a meeting with your team, you decide to run an A/B test. Version A includes an image of three shoes and a model with the caption “Put your best foot forward. Check out our summer collection.” There is a call to action button that says ‘order now’. What is the best practice to follow when developing your version B?",
    "answers": ["Only vary the image creating version B."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true about the accuracy of attribution results?",
    "answers": [
      "The accuracy of the attribution results depends on the quality of the data input."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are working on a campaign with the objective to drive app downloads. You have created an audience on Facebook for your campaign. But, you also have a list of emails from people who have downloaded an app from you before, and you plan to create a custom audience using that list. You also want to run ads on television and radio. Now, you would like to know which platform would be most effective for delivering your message. You work with a market research agency to help you with this. Which study could help you?",
    "answers": ["You can run a Marketing Mix Modeling study"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true about connecting touchpoints to one individual person? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "It's challenging for advertisers to connect the data from a person’s interactions with ads on mobile devices with that same person’s interactions on computers.",
      "Historically, advertisers have relied on cookies to connect a sequence of touchpoints to a person.",
      "Meta Pixel, the SDK and the conversions API allow you to tie actions directly to real people due to Facebook's ability to track persistent login and a unique identifier associated with a person’s Facebook account."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What data might you include when presenting on consideration KPIs?",
    "answers": ["Charts and graphs on traffic and engagement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What might be a good tactic when thinking about opening and closing your presentation?",
    "answers": [
      "Connect the opening and closing with a story, a question, or an interesting fact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When creating a presentation, what should you focus on last?",
    "answers": ["Ways you'll iterate future campaigns"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were presenting your data results, and wanted to talk about your revenue as a ratio to what you spent, what number would you include?",
    "answers": ["ROAS"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How could you open your presentation?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to talk about an experiment you ran that showed the difference between two audiences being marketed to. Which of the following would you talk about?",
    "answers": ["A/B Testing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's the day of your presentation, and you are NOT confusing your audience. Why?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What data might you include when presenting on awareness KPIs?",
    "answers": ["Charts and graphs on reach and impressions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You're anticipating audience questions, especially one asking how the budget was spent and if money was wasted. You'd then include a slide addressing what?",
    "answers": ["ROAS, ROI, and possible CAC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to talk about an experiment you ran that showed how much your marketing increased behavior. Which of the following would you talk about?",
    "answers": ["Lift study"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's the day of your presentation, and you do NOT need to call IT. Why?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to increase both reach and customer engagement on social media. Which approach combines free and paid strategies to achieve this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "Create engaging content while using targeted ads to reach a wider audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A nonprofit is planning a fundraising campaign and wants to maximize donations without incurring platform fees. Which social media tool is best suited for this goal?",
    "answers": ["Facebook's charitable giving tools"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A nonprofit wants to raise awareness for endangered species. They have created a campaign that shares disappearing images on Snapchat with the hashtag #LastSelfie. What is the primary purpose of this strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "To engage supporters and drive viral awareness through social sharing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company has recently joined Instagram. What is one way they can strategically use both free and paid tools on the platform to achieve business goals?",
    "answers": ["Post regularly and run targeted ad campaigns"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business wants to grow its brand using social media. What is the first step they should take?",
    "answers": [
      "Identify their target audience and select the best platforms for engagement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a key advantage of digital marketing compared to traditional marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "The ability to track engagement and adjust strategies in real time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business has a small budget but wants to grow its online presence. What is the best way for them to increase brand awareness for free?",
    "answers": [
      "Posting engaging content, responding to customer comments and encouraging user-generated content"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one major difference between traditional and digital marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "Digital marketing allows businesses to target specific audiences, while traditional marketing typically reaches a broad audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business is creating a marketing strategy and wants to include social media. How does social media marketing fit into digital marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "It is a type of digital marketing that focuses on engaging audiences through social media platforms"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new business is launching on social media and wants to gain followers and drive sales. What strategy should they use?",
    "answers": [
      "Posting engaging content regularly and using paid ads to reach new customers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A nonprofit organization wants to raise awareness and funds for a cause using social media. What is the best way to achieve this?",
    "answers": [
      "Sharing stories, using visuals and encouraging supporters to spread the message"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A clothing brand wants to connect with customers online without directly pushing sales. Which marketing strategy would be most effective?",
    "answers": [
      "Posting fashion tips, style guides and trend reports on their blog and social media"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local restaurant wants to build stronger relationships with customers through Facebook. Which approach aligns with how other businesses use the platform to engage their audience?",
    "answers": [
      "The restaurant can create a Facebook page to post updates, host events, and share content to encourage community interaction."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business is launching a new product and wants to promote it through video content. How can YouTube's features support this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "The business can create a YouTube channel, organize videos into playlists, and promote content with video ads."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business needs to manage customer communications efficiently using messaging platforms. Which key features would help accomplish this on both WhatsApp and Messenger?",
    "answers": [
      "WhatsApp offers contact labels to organize customers, while Messenger supports automated responses for quick replies."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A clothing brand wants to increase audience engagement on Instagram. Which strategy would best achieve this?",
    "answers": [
      "The brand can use Instagram Stories to post behind-the-scenes content and create interactive polls and questions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A job seeker wants to use LinkedIn to grow their professional network. What key features of LinkedIn can help them achieve this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "The job seeker can create a profile showcasing their job history, skills, and accomplishments, and connect with other professionals."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local bakery wants to share updates, post videos and images, and interact with customers online. Which platform would be the best choice?",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness influencer wants to attract more views and engagement on TikTok. What is the best way to achieve this?",
    "answers": [
      "Create short, engaging workout videos with trending music and relevant hashtags"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local gym just opened and wants to attract members through Facebook. What’s the best first step?",
    "answers": ["Create a Facebook Business Page and post regular updates"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness coach wants to stand out on YouTube while attracting more subscribers. What is the best strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Develop a series of well-produced workout challenges with interactive elements and audience participation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Messenger feature allows businesses to let customers book appointments directly within the app?",
    "answers": ["Appointment scheduling"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A travel blogger wants to grow their audience on Instagram. They are considering different ways to attract new followers. Which strategy would work best?",
    "answers": [
      "Use Instagram Reels to create short, engaging travel videos with trending audio and hashtags"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business consultant wants to generate leads on LinkedIn. They know they need to expand their reach but aren’t sure how to get started. What is the best strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Share valuable content, engage with industry discussions, and connect with potential clients"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A personal trainer wants to grow their client base using TikTok. They see that fitness content is popular on the platform but aren’t sure how to make their videos stand out. What is the best strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Create high-energy, short workout clips with trending sounds and clear fitness tips"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra runs a flower business and wants to promote her new website for online orders. Which of the following is an example of a measurable success metric Imra could use to track her goal?",
    "answers": ["Increase website visits to 10,000 in May"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is it crucial to establish clear marketing goals before launching a campaign?",
    "answers": ["To align efforts and evaluate success"]
  },
  {
    "question": "James manages marketing for a cleaning service launching a new product, SnackWall. His manager gives him the goal: \"Achieve a 25% client enrollment in SnackWall.\" What additional information does James need to make this a SMART goal?",
    "answers": ["A timeline to achieve the goal"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra wants to launch a campaign to boost her online flower sales. She sets the goal: \"Increase online flower sales by 50%.\" What changes should Imra make for this goal to fully meet all components of the SMART framework?",
    "answers": ["Add a timeline and clarify how sales will be tracked"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra sets a goal to achieve $50,000 in online flower sales within 6 months. How does this goal meet the ‘measurable’ criterion of SMART?",
    "answers": [
      "It includes a clear sales target that can be tracked over time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "James, the social media manager at DCB Cleaning, needs to track the performance of the new SnackWall service. His goal is to enroll 25% of existing clients within 6 months. Which KPI should James track?",
    "answers": ["Number of SnackWall subscribers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra is launching a new floral subscription service. Her marketing goal is to gain 500 subscribers in 3 months. Which of the following best describes this goal?",
    "answers": ["A specific and measurable marketing goal"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jordan’s team sets a marketing goal to \"increase customer sign-ups by 25% in six months.\" They create a subgoal to \"launch a referral program next quarter\" and track referral conversions to support this. How does a subgoal differ from a KPI or a SMART goal?",
    "answers": [
      "A subgoal outlines a smaller step toward achieving a broader goal, while a KPI measures progress and a SMART goal ensures the goal is clearly defined"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Luis manages a home décor brand and is launching an email marketing campaign. Why are KPIs essential for his decision-making?",
    "answers": [
      "They help track key metrics like email open rates and conversion rates to refine his strategy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Liam, the owner of a digital marketing agency, sets a goal: \"Increase client retention by 15%.\" What change would make this goal time-bound?",
    "answers": [
      "Setting a deadline, such as \"Increase client retention by 15% within the next six months.\""
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maya is running a paid advertising campaign for her e-commerce store. Which KPI should she monitor to measure ad effectiveness?",
    "answers": [
      "Return on ad spend (ROAS) tracks revenue generated per dollar spent on ads"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Raj wants to grow his podcast audience. His goal is to \"increase podcast downloads by 20% in 4 months.\" What is the primary purpose of this goal?",
    "answers": ["To increase audience engagement and reach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mia owns a handmade jewelry business and sets a goal to \"increase sales by 500% in two weeks.\" What is the main issue with this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "It is not achievable given the short timeframe and drastic increase in sales required"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Amara is running a crowdfunding campaign for her sustainable fashion brand. She wants to ensure her marketing efforts are effective. Why are KPIs essential in this situation?",
    "answers": [
      "They allow her to track performance and adjust strategies if needed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mila is identifying the target audience for her artisanal candle business. She describes her ideal customers as individuals aged 25 to 45 who live in urban areas and have a passion for home decor. What characteristic is Mila using to describe her target audience?",
    "answers": ["Demographics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tom owns a local bakery and wants to identify his target audience. Based on the practices described by Imra at Calla & Ivy, what should Tom consider when defining his target audience?",
    "answers": ["Common needs, demographics, interests and behaviors."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sara is researching her target audience for an eco-friendly cleaning product. She finds that many potential customers frequently visit sustainability blogs and follow eco-conscious influencers. What characteristic is Sara identifying?",
    "answers": ["Behaviors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sophia runs an online boutique selling handmade jewelry. She wants to refine her marketing to attract more repeat customers. What is the most effective strategy for Sophia to define and target the right audience?",
    "answers": [
      "Analyze purchase history, website traffic and customer engagement data to create personalized campaigns"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Daisy runs an online jewelry boutique and notices that many repeat customers follow fashion influencers and frequently engage with Instagram posts about sustainable fashion. What category does this characteristic fall under?",
    "answers": ["Interests"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rachel wants to understand how to move customers through the stages of the customer journey. What should she focus on?",
    "answers": [
      "Identifying key moments where marketing can encourage progress"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Victor is launching a new brand of eco-friendly sneakers. He wants to attract customers who have never heard of his product before. What should he focus on?",
    "answers": ["Creating awareness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Carlos owns a custom furniture business. He notices that potential customers visit his website and browse different designs but don’t make a purchase right away. To keep them engaged, he sends follow-up emails showcasing customer reviews and behind-the-scenes videos of the craftsmanship. What stage of the customer journey is Carlos focusing on?",
    "answers": ["Interest"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lena owns a subscription meal service and wants to increase sign-ups. She notices that potential customers visit her website and browse meal plans but don’t sign up. To keep them engaged, she offers an interactive quiz to help them find the best meal plan for their needs. Which stage of the customer journey is she targeting?",
    "answers": ["Interest"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lucas owns a specialty coffee brand. His research shows that his core customers are working professionals who buy high-end coffee beans regularly. However, he notices that students occasionally purchase his products as gifts. How should Lucas categorize these groups?",
    "answers": [
      "Working professionals are the primary audience, and students are the secondary audience."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tasha owns an online bookstore. She notices that many visitors read book reviews on her website but don’t make a purchase. To encourage them, she introduces a “Buy One, Get One 50% Off” promotion for first-time buyers. Which stage of the customer journey is she targeting?",
    "answers": ["Conversion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sophie is launching a subscription box service for organic skincare products. She wants to define her ideal customers so she can tailor her marketing strategy. Which of the following would be the most effective way to define her target audience?",
    "answers": [
      "Identify their demographics, interests and behaviors to create a detailed customer persona"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra wants customers to spread the word about Calla & Ivy's bouquets. What strategy should she use?",
    "answers": ["Offer referral incentives and request online reviews"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra is a florist who wants to increase her social media presence. Her target audience is women between 30 and 55 years old, and she needs a platform to showcase images of her flower bouquets. Which social media platform is the best fit for Imra's needs?",
    "answers": ["Instagram"]
  },
  {
    "question": "James, who runs a corporate catering service, wants to drive new subscriptions through social media. He has humorous, image-based content ideas and is already active on Facebook. Which platform would complement his current presence and content strategy?",
    "answers": ["Instagram"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A DIY brand creates how-to craft tutorial videos and wants to attract adult hobbyists to increase tutorial views. The brand needs a platform that supports long-form video content and engages its target audience. Which platform is most suitable for this goal?",
    "answers": ["YouTube"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A mobile pet grooming service offers convenient, on-location grooming for pet owners in busy urban areas. Based on audience-mapping strategies, who is the primary target audience?",
    "answers": ["Pet owners living in urban neighborhoods"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A bakery wants to increase online orders while minimizing costs. Based on the guidelines for selecting platforms with limited resources, which option should they choose?",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local gym wants to use social media to increase membership sign-ups. What strategy would be the most effective?",
    "answers": ["Hosting live workout sessions and interactive Q&As"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business wants to use blogging to increase brand credibility. What is the most effective strategy?",
    "answers": ["Posting high-quality, informative content regularly"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A financial services company wants to prevent employees from sharing confidential information on social media. What is the best policy to implement?",
    "answers": [
      "Clearly define what is confidential and provide training on responsible social media use"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new coffee shop wants to build an online community and attract local customers. What is the best first step?",
    "answers": [
      "Identify their target audience and select platforms where they are most active"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to define who manages official social media accounts clearly. What is the best practice?",
    "answers": [
      "Assign specific employees or a social media team to manage official accounts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local boutique wants to showcase visually appealing products and drive sales through social media. Which platform should they focus on?",
    "answers": ["Instagram"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local bakery wants to improve its social media presence to attract more customers. Which of the following is the best way to ensure its profile is easily recognizable and discoverable?",
    "answers": [
      "Use the bakery's name along with a keyword like \"bakery\" in the username"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small boutique is setting up its Instagram Business Account. What is the first step the owner must take before accessing Instagram’s business features?",
    "answers": ["Switch from a personal account to a business account"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A restaurant is creating its Facebook Business Page. Which component is most important to help customers take action, such as making a reservation or placing an order?",
    "answers": ["A call-to-action button"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes a key element of a strong brand presence?",
    "answers": [
      "A consistent profile name, logo, and brand voice across platforms"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lisa is launching a handmade jewelry business and wants to establish a professional social media presence. What is the best first step to take when setting up her profile?",
    "answers": ["Selecting a strong username and adding contact details"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jessica is launching a Facebook Business Page for her home decor shop. She wants to encourage customer interaction. Which element should she set up first?",
    "answers": ["A call-to-action button leading to her online store"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fashion brand is selecting fonts, colors, and imagery for their marketing materials. Which EPIC framework element are they working on?",
    "answers": ["Identity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Samantha is launching an Instagram account for her handmade pottery business. She wants to access business tools such as analytics and contact buttons. What should she do first?",
    "answers": ["Switch from a personal account to a Business Account"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A food brand has been in business for decades, and customers associate it with tradition and reliability. What branding element strengthens this perception?",
    "answers": ["Trust"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A skincare brand’s website highlights its founder’s struggle with sensitive skin and the journey to create gentle, all-natural products. How does this story impact the brand?",
    "answers": [
      "It builds customer trust by showing authenticity and a personal mission"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A cosmetics company promotes its mission of using only organic and ethically sourced ingredients. How does this purpose influence its brand?",
    "answers": [
      "It helps attract customers who value sustainability and ethical production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A café selects an earthy color palette, a hand-drawn logo, and rustic typography to emphasize its commitment to organic and fair-trade products. How does this contribute to its brand identity?",
    "answers": ["It visually reinforces the brand’s values and mission"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new restaurant has set up its Instagram Business Account but wants to make it easy for customers to contact them. What should they do next?",
    "answers": [
      "Add contact options such as email, phone, or directions to their profile"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A restaurant wants to build long-term customer loyalty. How can branding help achieve this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "Creating a strong emotional connection by aligning with customer values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one way to make your social media text more engaging?",
    "answers": ["Use the word \"you\" to create a personal connection"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a best practice when selecting an image for a social media post?",
    "answers": [
      "Choose an image that aligns with your brand identity and storytelling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one way to optimize a social media video for audience engagement?",
    "answers": ["Capture attention within the first five seconds"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a key benefit of using a content calendar for social media?",
    "answers": ["It helps plan and organize posts in advance"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of curated content?",
    "answers": [
      "Sharing an industry expert’s article on your social media page"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small bakery wants to use storyboarding to plan its upcoming social media content. Which of the following would be the best first step?",
    "answers": [
      "Defining the goal of the content, such as increasing engagement or driving sales"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following types of social media content is most likely to encourage audience participation?",
    "answers": ["A post that asks a question and invites users to comment"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a key reason why businesses should use a content calendar for social media management?",
    "answers": ["It allows for better planning and consistency in messaging"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Carlos owns a pet grooming business and recently started posting short grooming tutorials on social media. Soon, he noticed an increase in engagement and more customers booking appointments. Why was his approach successful?",
    "answers": [
      "He provided valuable content that built trust and encouraged interaction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A home decor business is posting about a new furniture collection on Facebook. They include a high-quality image and a brief caption. What else should they add to increase engagement?",
    "answers": [
      "A strong call to action that encourages followers to visit their store or website"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A coffee shop is posting an image of its new seasonal drink. What is the best way to make it visually engaging?",
    "answers": ["Use natural lighting, a close-up shot, and the rule of thirds"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A tutoring company wants to create an engaging educational video for social media. How can they make the content more engaging for their audience?",
    "answers": [
      "Start with a relatable problem and use captions for accessibility"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local restaurant wants to share a post about its new seasonal menu. What is the best way to make the text engaging?",
    "answers": [
      "Use storytelling to highlight the ingredients and inspiration behind the dishes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness studio is sharing a Facebook post about a new class schedule. How can they encourage audience engagement?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask a question and encourage followers to comment with their favorite workout time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A bakery is announcing a new seasonal pastry on Instagram. What is the best way to write an engaging caption?",
    "answers": [
      "Use a friendly tone, emojis, and a short story about the pastry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question prompt goes hereA clothing brand is posting a new outfit collection on Instagram. What is the best way to write a caption that drives engagement?",
    "answers": ["Use a conversational tone, storytelling, and a call to action"]
  },
  {
    "question": "David is managing a bakery’s Instagram account. He wants to use platform-specific strategies to increase engagement. What should he post?",
    "answers": ["A short video showing the process of decorating a cake"]
  },
  {
    "question": "James is creating a storyboard for a YouTube tutorial. What should he focus on to ensure clarity?",
    "answers": ["Organizing the visuals and dialogue into a logical sequence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media team realizes their engagement is lower than expected for their scheduled posts. What should they do to improve their content calendar?",
    "answers": ["Review analytics and adjust posting times or content types"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A travel blogger has a collection of stunning photos from past trips. How can they repurpose this content creatively?",
    "answers": ["Create a slideshow video with captions and share it on TikTok"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A clothing brand wants to encourage more people to share its posts. How can they use the concept of \"social currency\" to increase shares?",
    "answers": [
      "Create content that makes people look knowledgeable or trendy when they share it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company receives a mix of critical and abusive comments on a new product post. How should they handle these interactions?",
    "answers": [
      "Respond professionally to valid criticism but remove harmful or offensive comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small bakery wants to expand its Instagram following. How can they use hashtags effectively to increase visibility?",
    "answers": [
      "Use a mix of trending, niche, and branded hashtags in their posts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team is creating a content calendar to manage their social media strategy. What key components should they include?",
    "answers": ["Posting dates, content types, platforms, and campaign goals"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to maximize engagement by repurposing content. What type of content is ideal for repurposing?",
    "answers": ["Evergreen content that remains relevant over time"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing agency wants to add variety to its social media posts. How can they effectively use curated content?",
    "answers": ["Share relevant industry articles with added insights"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business owner has been posting on social media but isn’t seeing much engagement. They decide to analyze their post-performance using KPIs. Which of the following is an example of an engagement KPI?",
    "answers": ["Likes, comments and shares"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team notices a social media post had a high reach but very few interactions. What should they do to improve engagement?",
    "answers": ["Create more interactive content, such as questions or polls"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to improve its content strategy by using Meta Business Suite. Which of the following actions can they take to optimize their posts?",
    "answers": [
      "Analyze post performance in Meta Business Suite Insights and adjust content accordingly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to track whether their social media efforts are leading to sales. Which metric should they focus on?",
    "answers": ["Website conversions from social media"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jake's company wants to track how many social media users visit their website and complete a purchase. Which KPI should they focus on?",
    "answers": ["Click-through rate and conversion rate"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sophia manages multiple social media pages and wants to streamline her content posting. How can Meta Business Suite help?",
    "answers": [
      "It allows her to schedule and publish posts across Facebook and Instagram from one dashboard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Chris wants to assess how well his Facebook Page is performing over time. Which section of Facebook Insights provides an overview of key metrics, including engagement, reach and top-performing posts?",
    "answers": ["The Insights Home dashboard"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ethan wants to post at a time when most of his Instagram followers are online. Where can he find this information in Instagram Insights?",
    "answers": ["The Audience tab, under “Followers”"]
  },
  {
    "question": "David notices that engagement is highest on his posts that go live in the evening. How should he adjust his content calendar?",
    "answers": ["Schedule more posts in the evening when engagement is highest"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tina wants to know if her audience finds her posts interesting and valuable. Which metric should she track?",
    "answers": ["Comments and shares"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Liam notices that his recent posts have a low engagement rate despite high impressions. What does this indicate?",
    "answers": [
      "The content is being seen but is not resonating with the audience."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lisa sees that younger audiences engage more with her video content, while older audiences engage more with blog links. How should she adjust her strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Create more video content for younger audiences and more blog links for older audiences"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jordan’s audience frequently comments that they enjoy behind-the-scenes content. How should he adjust his social media strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Increase behind-the-scenes content while continuing to track audience engagement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why might a business choose to invest in paid social media advertising?",
    "answers": [
      "To increase the reach of their posts beyond their current followers."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a key difference between paid social media ads and organic posts?",
    "answers": [
      "Paid ads are guaranteed to be displayed to a targeted audience."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which platform allows you to send direct sponsored messages to a targeted audience?",
    "answers": ["LinkedIn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one of the main components of a paid social media ad?",
    "answers": ["Call to action"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An account's organic posts are getting fewer views, and follower growth has slowed. What should be done to increase visibility among new potential customers?",
    "answers": [
      "Invest in paid ads to reach people outside of their current follower base"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A content creator wants to understand how organic and paid content differ in appearance. What is one key visual distinction?",
    "answers": [
      "Paid ads are marked as “sponsored” and often include a call-to-action button"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small retail store wants to increase foot traffic using Instagram. Which ad format should be used?",
    "answers": ["A location-based ad promoting her store to nearby users"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing manager for a B2B company wants to share a downloadable case study with a professional audience. Which platform would best match this goal?",
    "answers": [
      "LinkedIn, because it supports whitepapers and business content"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign features strong copy and visuals, but users drop off after clicking. What’s the most likely issue?",
    "answers": ["The landing page experience doesn’t match the ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A pet grooming company runs an ad showing a happy dog in a tub, but the caption says “Celebrate Summer with 20% Off Cat Collars.” What is the problem with this ad?",
    "answers": [
      "The copy and visuals do not match, which can confuse the audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A jewelry company uses ads to reach people most likely to buy engagement rings. They define their audience as “men aged 28–38, recently engaged, living in metropolitan areas.” What does this example demonstrate?",
    "answers": ["Audience targeting using demographics and life events"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A digital course creator notices users are viewing her ad but not taking the next step. The ad ends with “Thanks for watching!” What change could improve performance?",
    "answers": ["Add a CTA like “Start Learning Today” to guide action"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand launches two ads with the same copy and visuals, but one ad gets significantly more views. The only difference is the bid strategy. What explains this?",
    "answers": [
      "The ad with the higher bid is likely to win more placement opportunities in auctions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An internal team is developing an ad but struggling with copy and image cohesion. What collaborative step could help?",
    "answers": [
      "Share a draft version early with the designer to align on tone and style"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first step you should take when creating a social media ad campaign?",
    "answers": ["Define your business objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which metric would you use to measure the effectiveness of a campaign aimed at increasing brand awareness?",
    "answers": ["Ad Recall Lift"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an effective way to create compelling visual assets for social media ads?",
    "answers": ["Use the Rule of Thirds for composition"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a key element of writing effective ad copy?",
    "answers": ["Create a strong opening that grabs attention"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local boutique is launching an ad campaign with the goal of increasing product sales through its website. The team wants to track the campaign’s return on investment. Which KPI would best measure the effectiveness of this campaign?",
    "answers": ["Return on ad spend (ROAS)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness brand is shooting video content to use in Facebook and Instagram Stories. They want to make sure the content performs well on mobile devices. What filming approach should they use?",
    "answers": ["Record vertical videos to fit mobile screens"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A startup without in-house designers hires a freelance animator to help with a new ad campaign. What is a benefit of working with an external creative professional?",
    "answers": [
      "External experts bring specific skills not available internally"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A designer receives a creative brief for a paid ad campaign and reviews the section describing the problem the product solves and what sets it apart. What part of the brief is the designer most likely reading?",
    "answers": ["The offer and key benefit"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local bakery is taking photos of its seasonal treats for a holiday campaign. The team wants the visuals to feel polished and eye-catching on social media. Which practice will help create effective images?",
    "answers": [
      "Use natural light and focus on a clear subject with minimal clutter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business is advertising allergy-friendly dog treats. They want to catch the attention of dog owners who are concerned about ingredients. What is the best way to open the ad copy?",
    "answers": [
      "Mention the audience’s concern and highlight the problem being solved"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business posts behind-the-scenes videos and customer testimonials regularly without paying to boost them. What type of content is this?",
    "answers": ["Organic content shared with followers naturally"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand creates an ad with calming imagery of a yoga session, but the copy emphasizes fast delivery and bulk discounts. Why might this ad be less effective?",
    "answers": [
      "The visual and text send mixed messages that confuse the audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team is designing a campaign to increase newsletter signups. The copy emphasizes a one-time sale, and the visuals focus on trending products. What issue could reduce the campaign’s effectiveness?",
    "answers": ["The creative elements don’t match the goal of lead generation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand creates a horizontal video ad with small text that is viewed mainly on mobile devices. Viewers are skipping it after just a few seconds. What change would most likely improve performance?",
    "answers": ["Create a vertical video with clear visuals and large text"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A shoe company wants to show ads for running shoes to users who have shown interest in fitness gear, even when they're reading unrelated articles online. What type of advertising would best support this strategy?",
    "answers": ["Data-based advertising"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which system is responsible for creating, organizing, and updating the main content of a website?",
    "answers": ["Content Management System (CMS)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A user logs into a social media site on both their phone and laptop. The platform can connect their activity across both devices. Which data format makes this possible?",
    "answers": ["UID (User Identifier)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of data is collected directly by a company through its own website or app?",
    "answers": ["First-party data"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A music streaming app uses an algorithm to recommend playlists based on your listening habits. The app transforms stored information into unreadable strings of characters to protect user data. What is this privacy method called?",
    "answers": ["Hashing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser chooses to place an ad for luxury watches inside a financial news article. Which targeting method are they applying?",
    "answers": ["Contextual advertising"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A user visits a travel website. The page loads vacation articles while an ad appears for luggage they recently browsed. What systems are most likely responsible for delivering both the content and the ad?",
    "answers": ["CMS and ad server"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A streaming platform allows users to log in from different devices and still receive the same show recommendations. What enables this continuity across platforms?",
    "answers": ["User identifiers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A user signs in to an online bookstore and updates their profile preferences. The bookstore later uses this information to recommend new titles. What kind of data is being used?",
    "answers": ["First-party data"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media platform provides users with tools to manage their data sharing and ad preferences. What level of data protection is this an example of?",
    "answers": ["Company data policies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media company is fined for failing to obtain consent before collecting personal data from EU residents. Which regulation applies in this case?",
    "answers": ["GDPR"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A user clicks the AdChoices icon on a digital ad and learns why the ad was shown to them. Which industry group created this transparency tool?",
    "answers": ["DAA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A Facebook user clicks “Why You’re Seeing This Ad” and learns they were targeted based on interests and demographics. What company policy is this tool connected to?",
    "answers": ["Meta’s data policy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An app encrypts user data before storage, so it can’t be traced back to individuals. What privacy method is being used?",
    "answers": ["Hashing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser uses a person’s online shopping history, location and interests to tailor which products they see in their feed. What is the main reason for using this approach?",
    "answers": ["To increase ad relevance and engagement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local fitness studio wants more people in the neighborhood to discover and visit their new location. Which Facebook ad objective should they use?",
    "answers": ["Promote Your Business Locally"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Facebook ad objective is best if your primary goal is to get more people to click through to your website?",
    "answers": ["Get More Website Visitors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local tutoring service wants to gather contact details from parents interested in future sessions. What’s the best Facebook ad objective for this goal?",
    "answers": ["Get More Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Facebook ad objective is designed to increase your Page’s followers?",
    "answers": ["Promote Your Page"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small landscaping company wants to chat with people interested in booking services or asking about availability. What’s the best Facebook ad objective?",
    "answers": ["Send Message"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer is preparing an ad to showcase a new line of eco-friendly backpacks. What’s the best practice when choosing her image?",
    "answers": [
      "Use a clear photo of the product that supports the ad’s message"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A portrait photographer just opened a studio in Berlin and wants to reach people nearby. Which objective will help achieve that?",
    "answers": ["Promote Your Business Locally"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lisa wants to reach moms interested in eco-baby products, but doesn’t want to rely on automatic targeting. What should she select?",
    "answers": ["Create Your Own"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An Instagram user taps an Instagram Stories ad and is redirected to a website. What made this possible?",
    "answers": ["The call-to-action button in the story ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A skincare company launches a fast-paced Story ad showing multiple products in a few seconds. Which creative best practice are they applying?",
    "answers": ["Keep attention with speed"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A digital marketer wants to promote a holiday sale, but Facebook has filled their ad with outdated content. How can he ensure his ad communicates the current offer?",
    "answers": [
      "Manually update all copy and visuals to match the seasonal message"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer increased their ad budget from $20 to $50 and extended the campaign to 5 days. What change should she expect?",
    "answers": [
      "Higher estimated reach and longer ad visibility to the target audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing specialist at a technology company wants to reach an audience similar to their current followers. Which targeting method should she use?",
    "answers": ["Suggested Audience (automatic targeting)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An ad opens with a model, then transitions to brand imagery, and ends with a discount code. What structural benefit does this provide?",
    "answers": [
      "It creates an engaging narrative while still delivering a clear offer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A digital marketer posts a Story about their product and wants to reach more users beyond their followers. What benefit does promoting the Story provide?",
    "answers": [
      "Paid ads appear between Stories and can reach a targeted audience outside of followers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Facebook advertising tool is best suited for managing multiple Pages, Ad Accounts and assigning roles to a team?",
    "answers": ["Business Manager"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one benefit of using Facebook Page tools to create ads directly from a Page?",
    "answers": [
      "It's a fast and simple way to create basic ads with pre-filled content"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ad placement setting lets Meta automatically distribute your ad across different platforms to get the best results for your budget?",
    "answers": ["Advantage+ Placements (automatic)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid placement option for Facebook ads through Meta’s platform?",
    "answers": ["Instagram Explore"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which combination of factors determines whether your ad wins in the Meta ad auction?",
    "answers": ["Bid amount, estimated action rate and ad quality"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following actions should you take if you see a post asking you to join a WhatsApp, Discord, or other external group for help with the course?",
    "answers": [
      "Do not join the group. Report the post and flag it as suspicious."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When reporting an issue or requesting help regarding a specific course item in the Questions & Support tab, which details should you include? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Activity Name",
      "Screenshot (if applicable)",
      "Description of the issue",
      "Module number",
      "Course name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you identify official moderators in the Coursera Community? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "They have \"Group Moderator\" in their name.",
      "Annie H and Jasmin R are official Coursera moderators"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is not allowed in the Coursera Community? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Sharing quiz answer screenshots",
      "Sharing personal information such as phone number, email, or address",
      "Sharing links to external groups"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which category of campaign objectives is most appropriate for encouraging people to learn more about a product or service?",
    "answers": ["Consideration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to collect email addresses from people who have previously interacted with its ads. Which campaign objective best supports this goal?",
    "answers": ["Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which campaign objective is best suited for maximizing how many people see an ad and how often they see it?",
    "answers": ["Reach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of objective should be selected when the goal is to prompt potential customers to make a purchase?",
    "answers": ["Sales"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team aims to drive more users to a blog page that explains a new service offering. Which campaign objective should they choose?",
    "answers": ["Traffic"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How does defining a target audience before launching a Facebook ad campaign improve its effectiveness?",
    "answers": [
      "It ensures the ad is shown to people who are most likely to take action"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main difference between a Core Audience and a Lookalike Audience in Meta Ads Manager?",
    "answers": [
      "Core Audiences are built from user traits; Lookalike Audiences are based on existing customer data"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tools can you use to define and refine a Core Audience in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Location, demographics, interests and behaviors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one way the Meta Pixel improves Facebook ad campaign performance?",
    "answers": [
      "It tracks user actions on your website to enhance targeting and measure conversions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following sources can be used to build a Custom Audience?",
    "answers": [
      "Website traffic, customer lists, app activity and Meta engagement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ad format in Meta Ads Manager allows you to include up to 10 images or videos, each with its own link?",
    "answers": ["Carousel Ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What step comes immediately after selecting your ad format when creating an ad in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Add media and text"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does it mean if your ad set is marked as “Learning” in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": [
      "The system is testing delivery to learn how to optimize ad performance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a best practice when writing copy for different placements in a Facebook ad?",
    "answers": [
      "Put the most important information at the beginning of your text"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to update its time zone and currency settings before launching a Meta ad campaign. What step should be taken to configure these settings?",
    "answers": [
      "Click “Edit” in the Business Info section to adjust the time zone and currency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business is deciding between using the Facebook Page interface and Meta Ads Manager to create its next campaign. What is one key advantage of using Meta Ads Manager instead of the Facebook Page “Create Ads” button?",
    "answers": [
      "It offers more advanced targeting, placement, and testing features"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to display ads in various placements across Meta’s platforms and partner sites. Which of the following includes valid ad placements available in Meta Ads Manager?",
    "answers": [
      "Feed, Stories, In-stream videos, Search, Messages, and Apps & Sites"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser wants to understand how they’re billed for their Meta ads. Which method is used to determine what they pay?",
    "answers": [
      "They’re charged based on impressions, clicks, or actions, depending on the ad’s objective"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser wants to test different images and headlines for their Meta ad. Which level allows them to do this?",
    "answers": ["Ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team wants to review the performance of past campaigns using Ads Reporting tools and view conversion results. Which section of the Meta Ads Manager navigation bar should they use?",
    "answers": ["Analyze and Report"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser wants to evaluate how different creatives perform while targeting the same audience. What level of the campaign structure should they duplicate?",
    "answers": ["Ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to customize where its ads appear, target specific audiences, and use advanced tools like A/B testing. Which platform should they use?",
    "answers": ["Meta Ads Manager"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser selects a campaign objective focused on video views. How might Meta charge them for the ad?",
    "answers": ["Based on user actions, like completing a video view"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two advertisers are targeting the same audience. One has a higher bid, but their ad is shown less often. Why?",
    "answers": [
      "The other ad had a higher total value, factoring in quality and estimated action rate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to generate interest and recognition among people who haven't interacted with them before. What is the best campaign objective to use?",
    "answers": ["Awareness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign has a strict end date and a fixed budget to spend over that time. The advertiser wants Meta to distribute the spend as needed across days without going over the total. Which budget type supports this?",
    "answers": ["Lifetime budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A startup with a strict maximum bid of $2 per click wants to ensure Meta does not exceed this limit in any auction. Which bid strategy should be used?",
    "answers": ["Bid cap"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to encourage more likes, comments, and shares on its posts to grow its presence on the platform. Which Meta campaign objective should be used?",
    "answers": ["Engagement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business sets a daily budget of $40. On a particular day, the campaign performs exceptionally well. What is the maximum amount Meta might spend that day?",
    "answers": ["$50"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign uses Campaign Budget Optimization to manage budget across multiple ad sets. Meta notices that one ad set is performing better than the others. What will Meta do in this case?",
    "answers": [
      "Meta will allocate more budget to the better-performing ad set"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign manager wants Meta to spend consistently every day, regardless of performance fluctuations. Which type of budget should be used?",
    "answers": ["Daily budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business is preparing a two-week campaign. The team wants to align the budget with their marketing goals while staying within their means. What is the most appropriate budgeting approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Choose an amount that fits the campaign goals and available resources"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants potential customers to sign up for a weekly newsletter using a form that collects their name and email address. Which objective in Ads Manager is best suited to support this goal?",
    "answers": ["Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A mobile app company wants to drive downloads for its new budgeting app. Which campaign objective should they select?",
    "answers": ["App promotion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company plans to run a one-week campaign and wants the ad to stop automatically at the end. What budget setting requires a start and end date?",
    "answers": ["Daily budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to reach new people similar to their existing website visitors. What type of audience should they use?",
    "answers": ["Lookalike audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to reach people with specific job titles and education levels. Which audience feature supports this kind of targeting?",
    "answers": ["Demographic targeting in a core audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to reconnect with people who recently interacted with their Facebook Page. What type of audience should they use?",
    "answers": ["Custom audience from Facebook engagement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to track when people add products to their cart on their website. What tool should they use to make this possible?",
    "answers": ["Meta Pixel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to find new potential customers who are similar to their most active app users. Which audience type should they create?",
    "answers": ["Lookalike audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client is concerned about managing delivery across multiple platforms. What is one reason they should consider using Advantage+ placements?",
    "answers": [
      "It reduces manual workload by automatically optimizing across placements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to control how much they’re willing to pay for a conversion. What tool should they use?",
    "answers": ["Set a bid cap in Ads Manager"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client is setting up an ad set with a lifetime budget and wants to make sure the ad doesn’t run over weekends. What should they do?",
    "answers": ["Customize the schedule to exclude weekend time slots"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client is setting up a new ad set and notices that changing their audience size affects the reach number. What does the estimated audience reach help them understand?",
    "answers": [
      "The number of people likely to see their ad based on audience and budget"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A product launch is underway, and the goal is to generate excitement among potential customers. Which action most effectively aligns the ad with this goal in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Choosing the “Awareness” campaign objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business wants to create an engaging video ad using images and text but doesn’t have a video editor. What ad format in Ads Manager is best suited for this situation?",
    "answers": ["Slideshow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An ad preview shows the primary text is being cut off in mobile feeds. What should be done to address this issue?",
    "answers": [
      "Move the most important message to the beginning of the primary text"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness brand wants to say, “Are you too weak to lift weights?” Why could this statement violate Meta’s ad policies?",
    "answers": ["It references a personal physical trait in a negative way"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser sets a lifetime budget and selects a 10-day campaign window. What does the budget control in this scenario?",
    "answers": ["The total amount spent over the entire 10-day campaign"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team wants to test different audiences without restarting the learning phase for an existing ad set. Which approach should be taken?",
    "answers": ["Duplicate the ad set and edit the new version separately"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After completing all steps in Ads Manager, an advertiser skips the tracking section and clicks Publish. What is the likely result of skipping this step?",
    "answers": ["The ad will run, but performance data may be incomplete"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer notices an ad set is underperforming and labeled as “Learning Limited.” What would be the most appropriate first step to optimize reach and delivery?",
    "answers": ["Expand the audience targeting to increase reach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing analyst wants to understand weekly ad performance trends. What feature in Ads Manager should be used?",
    "answers": ["Breakdown by time"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An analyst reviews a conversion-focused campaign. Which metric would best reflect cost efficiency for this objective?",
    "answers": ["Cost per result"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three primary uses of a Facebook Page? (Choose three)",
    "answers": [
      "Have an online storefront for the business",
      "Connect with customers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How can a business increase the reach of an organic post on its Page without creating a campaign in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Boost the post"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you begin a new campaign on Ads Manager, what is the first step in the process?",
    "answers": ["Align your marketing goal with a campaign objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business set up a campaign. During the process, it tested different placements and observed a higher estimated total reach when it selected automatic placements. What caused this result?",
    "answers": [
      "Advantage+ Placements more efficiently distributed the ad bids."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "DCB Cleaning ran a campaign targeting businesses looking to switch their cleaning services, offering a six-month commitment for $1,000. The campaign ran for three months, at $200 per month, and gained six new clients. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["10"]
  },
  {
    "question": "DCB Cleaning ran a campaign to get people to download their app, knowing that they generate $200 in revenue for every five downloads. The campaign cost $1,000, and they received 75 downloads. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko is launching a new product line on its website: bandanas for dogs. Each bandana costs $10, and in the month of its $800 campaign, they sold out of all 200 bandanas. What was the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["2.5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It costs Calla & Ivy $10 in materials to make each free bouquet. They spent $200 on their marketing campaign, and 50 of their 200 sign-ups each resulted in a $50 purchase. What is their ROI?",
    "answers": ["2.57"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko has recently run several campaigns and is calculating the Cost Per Result for each. They began with a reach campaign, which generated 1,000 impressions for a $200 campaign. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.20"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Another campaign for Inu + Neko was a lead generation campaign. They know that every five leads converts into a $20 sale. The campaign cost $800, and they generated 1,000 leads. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.80"]
  },
  {
    "question": "They ran another lead generation campaign, which cost them $200 per month for four months. Over those four months, they brought in 2,000 leads, double the amount of leads as before. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$0.40"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko ran a campaign to increase views on their grooming videos. They allocated a $10 daily budget for the month of September, which has 30 days. They received 75 plays by the end. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$4.00"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Inu + Neko is trying to drive more traffic to the new products on their site, and set up a conversion campaign, allotting $500 a month for six months. At the end of that time, they made $20,000 in sales from 600 customers. What was the Cost Per Result?",
    "answers": ["$5.00"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Calla & Ivy want to figure out the lifetime value of their customers. They know that the average customer’s value is $50 a month, and the average lifespan of a customer is 5 years (60 months). What is the LTV?",
    "answers": ["$3,000"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Next, Calla & Ivy want to determine the average purchase frequency rate. There were 50 people in this demographic who made purchases last month. What is the Average Purchase Frequency per month? You need to use the information in Question 2 to figure this one out.",
    "answers": ["2"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business runs a three-week campaign to promote its $60 product. They spend $300 on advertising and generate $900 in revenue from sales directly tied to the campaign. What is their Return on Ad Spend (ROAS)?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A tech company has an average order value of $100, customers buy 4 times a year, and the average customer stays with them for 3 years. What is the Lifetime Value (LTV) of a customer?",
    "answers": ["$1,200"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following would typically be considered a strong ROAS?",
    "answers": ["6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An online software company’s average customer spends $100 annually and stays for 10 years. What is the LTV?",
    "answers": ["$1,000"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business runs a holiday campaign and sees a ROAS of 5. They are excited until they realize their ROI is much lower than expected. What does this suggest?",
    "answers": ["The campaign had high additional costs beyond advertising"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An online event organizer spends $750 on a lead generation campaign. The campaign yields 50 leads. What is the cost per lead?",
    "answers": ["$15"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An e-commerce company’s ad campaign results in a $3 cost per click. The product they sell costs $10, and only 10% of clicks convert to sales. What’s the issue?",
    "answers": [
      "The cost per result may be too high relative to the revenue earned per conversion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A software company spends $5,000 on marketing and gains 100 new customers. What is their customer acquisition cost?",
    "answers": ["$50"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business wants to know how much they spent to gain each new customer last quarter. Which metric should they calculate?",
    "answers": ["Customer Acquisition Cost"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign generates $15,000 in revenue. Production, shipping, and marketing costs total $5,000. What is the ROI?",
    "answers": ["2.0"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team analyzes their brand lift results and sees a 21.8% recall in the test group and 7.9% in the control group. How is the brand lift percentage derived?",
    "answers": ["Subtract the control group recall from the test group recall"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team observes that the control group had a 9% recall rate, while the test group had 21%. They’re trying to evaluate the strength of the campaign. What role does the control group recall play in interpreting brand lift?",
    "answers": [
      "It establishes a baseline, so the lift reflects only the incremental impact of the ad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer reviews a test report and sees that the confidence level is 42%. The team is unsure how to proceed. What does this low confidence level suggest?",
    "answers": [
      "The results may not be statistically strong enough to guide future decisions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After reviewing a conversion lift test, a performance marketer reports a return on ad spend (ROAS) of 8.5. What does this ROAS indicate about the campaign’s performance?",
    "answers": ["The campaign generated $8.50 in revenue for every $1 spent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A test group includes participants who never logged into the platform and didn’t see the ad. The team notices that the measured brand lift is lower than expected. How does Intention to Treat (ITT) contribute to this outcome?",
    "answers": [
      "ITT can lower observed impact by including people who weren’t exposed to the ad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A florist runs an ad campaign to increase online bouquet sales during the holiday season. She wants to measure if the ads lead to more completed purchases. Which test type would best assess this objective?",
    "answers": ["Conversion Lift Test"]
  },
  {
    "question": "While setting up a conversion lift test, a marketer is asked to select data sources and events. Why is selecting the right data source and event important for the test?",
    "answers": [
      "It defines what conversions Meta will track and measure for lift"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A Brand Lift Test includes the required ad recall question and one additional question about brand familiarity. What is one benefit of including multiple polling questions in a Brand Lift Test?",
    "answers": [
      "It provides more insight into different aspects of brand perception"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After completing a Brand Lift Test, a marketing team receives a summary report that includes how their results compare to the average outcomes from similar tests conducted in their region. Why is this type of comparison valuable?",
    "answers": [
      "It helps evaluate the relative strength of the campaign's impact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team runs a conversion lift test and finds a measurable increase in sales attributed to the campaign. How can they use this information moving forward?",
    "answers": [
      "To demonstrate that the campaign was effective and worth the investment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An analyst asks how Media Mix Modeling determines the value of each marketing channel. What should the analyst be told about how this method works?",
    "answers": [
      "It uses historical data and regression models to estimate each channel’s influence on results"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign team notices that a Facebook coupon ad appears to drive most conversions, but an earlier Instagram awareness campaign also likely contributed. What should the team do to better understand how all ads contributed?",
    "answers": [
      "Review their attribution model to make sure it accounts for multiple touchpoints"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business wants to improve its ability to measure conversions from its ads across online and offline channels. Which solution does Meta offer to help connect the full customer journey?",
    "answers": [
      "Tools like the Meta Pixel, SDK, and Conversions API to track across platforms"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After completing a successful A/B test, a marketer is deciding what to do next. What is the best way to continue optimizing their campaign?",
    "answers": [
      "Shift the budget to the winning version and create a new test based on it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A digital marketing analyst is reviewing options for assigning credit to ad touchpoints along the customer journey. Which attribution model credits the last ad a user clicked before converting?",
    "answers": ["Last-click attribution model"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer is comparing attribution models and notices one model uses a fixed rule to assign credit before analyzing any data. What type of model are they most likely looking at?",
    "answers": ["A rules-based attribution model"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After running an A/B test, a marketing analyst sees that the two versions performed similarly and no confidence level is reported. What does this outcome suggest?",
    "answers": ["There was no clear winner, and a new test should be created"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign resulted in high conversions on Facebook, but the marketing team also ran upper-funnel ads on YouTube and Instagram. What does the attribution data suggest if only the Facebook ad is getting credit?",
    "answers": [
      "The model may be underestimating the impact of earlier touchpoints"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business runs ads on social media, their website, and physical stores. Why is tracking online and offline sales important when measuring marketing effectiveness?",
    "answers": [
      "To get a complete view of how all campaigns contribute to overall performance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer finishes an A/B test that identifies a clear winning ad version. What should they do next to continue improving campaign performance?",
    "answers": [
      "Use the winning version as the new baseline and run another test"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team is preparing a presentation about a social media campaign and wants to explain why specific campaign choices were made. How should the campaign goal be used in this explanation?",
    "answers": [
      "By showing how the goal guided their decisions and audience targeting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing analyst is building a chart to show how different audiences responded to an ad campaign, but the chart is overcrowded with labels and numbers. What should be done to make the chart easier to understand?",
    "answers": [
      "Simplify the chart by removing unnecessary details and focusing on key comparisons"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign’s results show that women aged 35–44 responded more strongly to the ads than other groups. How should this insight be applied when planning future campaigns?",
    "answers": [
      "Adjust future targeting to focus more on this high-performing demographic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A presenter is starting a presentation on a recent ad campaign and wants to capture the audience’s interest immediately. What is the best way to open the presentation?",
    "answers": [
      "Start with a rhetorical question, a story or an interesting fact related to their findings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media marketer is worried about looking stiff or awkward while speaking. What is one way to prepare body language in advance?",
    "answers": [
      "Practice deliberate movements, like stepping forward at key points"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign analyst is scheduled to present in a shared workspace and wants to ensure the presentation runs smoothly. What step should be taken before beginning?",
    "answers": [
      "Test the display setup and audio in advance to check for potential issues"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign aimed to increase website subscriptions, but the presentation only includes impressions and reach data. What key mistake is being made when choosing the metrics?",
    "answers": [
      "Presenting metrics that don’t align with their campaign goal of conversions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign shows the strongest performance with a specific age group, and the marketing team wants to highlight this in a presentation. What should be done with this insight?",
    "answers": [
      "Present the age group insight as a key finding and suggest targeting them in future campaigns"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing analyst is presenting campaign data and wants to help the audience easily compare actual results to campaign goals. What is the best way to make this comparison clear in the chart?",
    "answers": [
      "Arrange the data so that each actual result is displayed directly next to its goal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team presenting campaign results wants to build trust in the data being shown. What should be done when discussing where the data came from?",
    "answers": [
      "Clearly explain which tools and sources they used to collect the campaign data"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you verified that the email for your Meta Blueprint account matches the email for your Coursera account?",
    "answers": ["Yes!"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one primary function of social media in marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "It allows businesses to interact with their audience and build brand loyalty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to target specific audiences with a cost-effective strategy. Why would digital marketing be a better choice than traditional marketing?",
    "answers": ["It is cost-effective and allows better audience targeting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an important part of social media marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "Engaging with followers and responding to their comments and messages"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is deciding between traditional and digital marketing. They want to ensure they can measure the impact of their campaigns and adjust their strategy as needed. Why would digital marketing be a better fit?",
    "answers": [
      "Digital marketing allows businesses to track results and optimize campaigns in real time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to increase brand awareness and customer engagement using social media. What is the best approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Using a mix of organic posts and paid ads to reach and interact with the target audience."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to educate potential customers about its products without directly promoting them. Which digital marketing strategy should they use?",
    "answers": [
      "Creating blog posts and videos that provide useful information"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local store wants to use social media to reach more customers. How should they approach their marketing strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Use social media to share updates, promotions and engage with customers online"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a key benefit of combining organic and paid social media marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "It helps businesses engage with current followers while also reaching new audiences"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A skincare brand wants to grow its Instagram following and increase brand awareness. What is the best strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Post engaging content regularly, use relevant hashtags and interact with followers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which YouTube feature provides insights into video performance, audience engagement and demographics?",
    "answers": ["YouTube Analytics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An online clothing boutique wants to showcase its latest collection on Instagram. What is the best strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Use Instagram Reels to create visually appealing fashion showcases with trending music"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media manager wants to improve their networking opportunities on LinkedIn. What is the best strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "Engage with industry posts, share relevant insights, and connect with professionals in their field"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A skincare brand wants to use TikTok to promote its products. They have heard that viral trends are important but aren’t sure how to approach content creation. What should they do?",
    "answers": [
      "Participate in trending challenges and create engaging videos that showcase their products in a fun way"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness studio has a Facebook Business Page but isn’t seeing much engagement. What tool can they use to reach more people?",
    "answers": [
      "Facebook Ads to target potential gym members by location and interests"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A clothing store owner wants to improve customer service using WhatsApp Business. She needs a way to quickly respond to frequently asked questions without typing the same answers repeatedly. What should she do?",
    "answers": [
      "Set up automated responses and quick replies to answer common customer questions efficiently"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A recent college graduate is looking for their first job in digital marketing. They know LinkedIn can help but aren’t sure where to start. What should they do to increase their chances of being noticed by recruiters?",
    "answers": [
      "Complete their LinkedIn profile with a professional photo, detailed work experience, and relevant skills"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra is running an online advertising campaign to drive flower sales. She wants to measure how many visitors to her website actually make a purchase. Which KPI should she track?",
    "answers": ["Conversion rate (percentage of visitors who make a purchase)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mia owns an online jewelry store and wants to increase sales. She sets a goal to generate $10,000 in revenue over the next three months. Why is this goal important for her business?",
    "answers": [
      "It provides a clear target and a way to measure progress toward success"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a subgoal in business planning?",
    "answers": [
      "A subgoal breaks down a larger goal into smaller, actionable steps contributing to success"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Drew is growing his business through influencer partnerships. Which KPI would best measure the success of his influencer marketing efforts?",
    "answers": ["Engagement rate on sponsored social media posts"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nina owns a plant delivery service called GreenGlow. She sets a marketing goal to \"increase Instagram followers by 5,000 within 6 months.\" What is the primary purpose of this goal?",
    "answers": ["To build brand awareness and expand the audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Noah, a content strategist for a travel blog, wants to grow the blog’s audience. His team is considering different marketing strategies. How do KPIs help in this situation?",
    "answers": [
      "They ensure the team focuses on measurable goals instead of vague ambitions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "James sets a goal to enroll 25% of DCB Cleaning clients in SnackWall within 3 months. How does this goal meet the ‘specific’ criterion of SMART?",
    "answers": [
      "It clearly defines a target percentage, customer segment and deadline"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Carlos manages marketing for a local gym. Why is it important for him to set clear goals before launching a new membership campaign?",
    "answers": [
      "Goals ensure the marketing team is aligned and working toward a shared objective"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hannah owns a handmade furniture business. Her main business goal is to \"increase overall revenue by 20% this year.\" Which of the following is an appropriate subgoal?",
    "answers": [
      "\"Increase website traffic by 30% in six months through paid advertising.\""
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "James is reviewing SnackWall's performance but is unsure which metrics to prioritize. Why are KPIs essential for James?",
    "answers": ["They help focus on metrics that track progress toward goals"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Olivia owns a handmade candle business and wants to grow her online sales. She is brainstorming different marketing goals to help her business succeed. Which of the following is a SMART goal for Olivia?",
    "answers": [
      "\"Increase online candle sales by 15% over the next three months by running targeted social media ads.\""
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sasha runs an online store selling fitness apparel. Her goal is to boost sales. Which KPI should she track?",
    "answers": ["Revenue generated from online purchases"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Caleb manages the social media for a fitness studio, PeakPulse. He feels overwhelmed by the vast amount of available data. Why are KPIs crucial in this situation?",
    "answers": ["They help prioritize the metrics most relevant to goals"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra owns Calla & Ivy, a flower business. She wants to define her primary target audience for her online store. Based on her customer insights, what is the most effective way for Imra to identify her target audience?",
    "answers": ["Analyze customer demographics, interests and behaviors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Carlos runs a premium coffee subscription service. He wants to analyze where potential customers drop off before subscribing. What stage of the customer journey should he focus on?",
    "answers": ["Interest to desire"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra wants to understand how customers move from discovering Calla & Ivy to becoming repeat buyers. What should she analyze?",
    "answers": ["The customer journey"]
  },
  {
    "question": "David owns an electronics store and wants to increase holiday sales. He notices that many customers browse products and add them to their carts but don’t complete their purchases. To encourage them, he sends a special discount code to shoppers who abandoned their carts. Which stage of the customer journey is he targeting?",
    "answers": ["Desire"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Josh runs a high-end fitness brand. His marketing primarily targets young professionals who are willing to invest in premium gym memberships, but he also markets to college students who may subscribe in the future. How should Ethan categorize these audiences?",
    "answers": [
      "Young professionals are the primary audience, and college students are the secondary audience."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team is working on a campaign for a new high-performance running shoe. They need to define their target audience before launching ads. Which group would be the most relevant target audience?",
    "answers": [
      "Athletes and fitness enthusiasts who regularly buy running gear and participate in sports activities"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "James wants to increase SnackWall’s word-of-mouth marketing. What strategy should he use to encourage customers to advocate for the product?",
    "answers": ["Offer referral incentives and request online reviews"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sophia runs an online boutique for vintage apparel. She notices many customers add items to their carts but don’t complete their purchases. What stage of the customer journey should she focus on improving?",
    "answers": ["Conversion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maya runs an online store for running shoes. She notices that some customers have shown repeated interest in a particular model by watching product videos and adding it to their wishlists. To push them toward making a purchase, she offers a limited-time 10% discount. What stage of the customer journey is Maya focusing on?",
    "answers": ["Desire"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A luxury travel agency is defining its target audience. Which of the following best represents a well-defined customer persona for their marketing?",
    "answers": [
      "\"Jet-Setting Julia,\" a high-income professional who prioritizes exclusive, customized travel experiences"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sarah wants more of her candle customers to recommend her brand to friends. Which approach would be most effective?",
    "answers": ["Offer referral incentives and request online reviews"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is launching an online tutoring service that provides affordable, flexible sessions for international college students. Based on audience-mapping strategies, who should they primarily target?",
    "answers": ["College students studying abroad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A high-end fashion brand wants to showcase its luxury collections and drive website traffic. Which platform should they prioritize?",
    "answers": ["Instagram"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A tech company wants to improve its website’s search engine ranking through blogging. What should they focus on?",
    "answers": ["Using relevant keywords throughout their blog posts"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness brand wants to increase brand awareness through social media. What is the best approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Select platforms that align with their audience and content style"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A financial services company wants to prevent unauthorized employees from posting company-related content. What should they do?",
    "answers": [
      "Limit access to social media accounts to trained and approved employees"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A nonprofit organization wants to raise awareness and encourage donations. Which platform should they prioritize?",
    "answers": ["Facebook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A nonprofit organization wants to use social media to increase donations. What is the best approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Sharing compelling storytelling posts about beneficiaries and impact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A retail brand wants to encourage employees to engage with its social media pages while ensuring professionalism. What should they do?",
    "answers": [
      "Establish a policy that outlines appropriate engagement and brand tone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A tech company wants to network with industry professionals and share thought leadership content. Which platform should they prioritize?",
    "answers": ["LinkedIn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A bakery wants to optimize its social media profile for customer engagement. What should be prioritized when setting up their profile?",
    "answers": ["Writing a clear bio and adding a website link"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An artist is setting up a Facebook Business Page to sell custom paintings. What should she prioritize first?",
    "answers": ["Uploading a profile picture and adding business details"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand strategist is helping a company improve its messaging on social media to engage customers better. Which part of the EPIC framework does this relate to?",
    "answers": ["Connection"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new jewelry brand wants to build a strong emotional connection with its social media audience. What is the best approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Share the brand’s origin story and values through engaging posts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness brand’s motto is \"Empowering everyone to move,\" and it actively supports community wellness programs. How does this purpose benefit the brand?",
    "answers": [
      "It builds stronger customer connections by aligning with shared values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A luxury auto company consistently uses a minimalist black-and-white design with sleek, elegant fonts in its marketing. What is the purpose of this visual choice?",
    "answers": ["It conveys a sense of sophistication and exclusivity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business has just launched an Instagram Business Account but is unsure what type of username to choose. What is the best approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Select a simple and recognizable username that matches their brand name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A clothing brand wants to stand out in a crowded market. Which branding strategy will help customers recognize and remember their brand?",
    "answers": [
      "Developing a consistent brand identity, including colors, logos, and messaging"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A luxury handbag brand is known for its craftsmanship and durability, leading customers to return for repeat purchases. What element drives this loyalty?",
    "answers": ["Trust"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A bakery shares how a family recipe passed down for generations became the foundation of its business. What role does this story play in branding?",
    "answers": ["It differentiates the brand by giving it a unique backstory"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lisa owns a bakery and wants to grow her business using social media. Instead of just posting product photos, she starts sharing videos of her baking process. Why is this a strong strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "It makes her content engaging and helps customers connect with her brand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imra wants to promote a new floral arrangement on Facebook. She includes a well-lit image, a short caption, and a website link. What else should she add to improve engagement?",
    "answers": ["A relevant hashtag or mention to increase visibility"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness brand wants to post an image of a new workout class. What is the best strategy?",
    "answers": ["Use action shots, natural lighting and vibrant colors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An event planning company wants to showcase a recent wedding setup through a video post. What is the best way to ensure the video looks professional?",
    "answers": [
      "Use natural lighting, steady camera movements and high-quality audio"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An online clothing store wants to encourage more interaction on its Instagram posts. What is the best way to make the text more engaging?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask a question and invite followers to share their thoughts in the comments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A bookstore is creating a Facebook post to promote an upcoming author event. How can they make the text more engaging?",
    "answers": [
      "Use an engaging opening, a personal tone, and a clear call to action"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A home decor business is posting a before-and-after transformation on Instagram. What is the best way to make the images visually appealing?",
    "answers": [
      "Use high-quality images with good lighting and a clean background"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fitness brand is sharing a workout tutorial on Instagram. What should they focus on to optimize the post?",
    "answers": [
      "Use a high-quality video, an engaging caption, and relevant hashtags"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A home improvement company is creating a before-and-after video of a kitchen renovation for Instagram. What should they focus on to optimize the video for the platform?",
    "answers": [
      "Keep the video short, use a vertical format and include a strong opening shot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A travel blogger is sharing an Instagram post about a recent trip. How can they make the post more discoverable?",
    "answers": [
      "Use relevant hashtags and tag the location to increase visibility"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local coffee shop is launching a new seasonal drink and wants to increase engagement on Instagram. How should they use hashtags and mentions effectively?",
    "answers": [
      "Use a mix of branded and popular hashtags and tag relevant partners"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jake wants to improve his company's social media strategy by using a content calendar. What is the primary benefit of doing this?",
    "answers": ["It helps organize and schedule posts in advance"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wrote a successful blog post about industry trends. How could they repurpose this content for social media?",
    "answers": [
      "Turn key insights into an infographic and share it on LinkedIn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team wants to create a viral campaign for a new product launch. According to research on viral content, what is one key element they should focus on?",
    "answers": ["Evoking strong emotions in the audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A customer leaves a negative comment on a brand’s social media page about a delayed order. What is the best way for the brand to respond?",
    "answers": [
      "Acknowledge the concern, apologize, and offer to resolve the issue privately"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company with multiple social media managers wants to improve collaboration. How can a content calendar help?",
    "answers": [
      "It allows team members to contribute ideas and track scheduled content"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A travel brand has long-form YouTube videos. How can they repurpose this content effectively?",
    "answers": [
      "Edit key moments into short clips for TikTok and Instagram Reels"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A beauty brand wants to create engaging content on social media. What type of tutorial would be most effective?",
    "answers": ["A short video demonstrating how to apply a new makeup product"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small tech startup is trying to increase its LinkedIn presence. What type of post would be most effective?",
    "answers": ["An article explaining industry trends and insights"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fashion brand wants to create a storyboard for an upcoming product launch video. What should they include to make it effective?",
    "answers": [
      "A structured sequence of frames outlining key moments in the video"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business wants to increase customer engagement on its social media posts. What is one effective strategy to encourage interaction?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask open-ended questions to invite followers to share their opinions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new fitness app wants to build an engaged social media community. Which strategy would be most effective?",
    "answers": ["Host challenges and encourage user-generated content"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business notices their engagement drops mid-week. How can they adjust their content calendar to improve performance?",
    "answers": [
      "Analyze engagement data and reschedule posts for higher activity periods"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wrote a blog post on industry trends. How could they repurpose it for social media?",
    "answers": ["Turn key insights into an infographic for LinkedIn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A coffee shop wants to engage customers on social media. What type of behind-the-scenes content would be most effective?",
    "answers": ["A video showing how baristas create latte art"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Emma receives many customer messages and wants to respond quickly. How can Meta Business Suite help her?",
    "answers": [
      "It consolidates messages from Facebook and Instagram into one inbox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Natalie wants to know which type of content receives the most engagement. Where should she look in Facebook Insights?",
    "answers": ["The Content tab to review engagement metrics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lena wants to know how many people visited her Instagram profile after seeing one of her posts. Which metric should she check in Instagram Insights?",
    "answers": ["Profile Visits"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mia reviews her content calendar and sees that posts with product demos have high engagement, while text-based posts have low engagement. What should she do next?",
    "answers": [
      "Increase the number of product demo posts and reduce text-based posts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Alex’s goal is to increase awareness of his brand on social media. Which metric should he focus on?",
    "answers": ["Reach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Carlos wants to ensure his content is reaching the right audience. Which tool should he use to analyze follower demographics?",
    "answers": ["Facebook Insights and Instagram Insights"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ella wants to increase engagement on her social media posts. She decides to try different types of content to see what resonates with her audience. What is the best approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Experiment with different content formats and track engagement metrics to identify what works best"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Maria wants to track how well her brand's content is performing on social media. She needs to choose KPIs that align with her goal of increasing engagement. Which KPI should she prioritize?",
    "answers": ["Likes, comments and shares"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mark wants to know which posts are performing best on Facebook and Instagram. How can Meta Business Suite help?",
    "answers": [
      "It provides insights on reach, engagement, and audience demographics for each post"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Anna posts similar content on Facebook and Instagram but notices higher engagement on Instagram. What should she do?",
    "answers": [
      "Analyze platform-specific engagement trends and adjust her strategy accordingly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business notices that posting three times a week generates more engagement than posting daily. How should they adjust their content calendar?",
    "answers": [
      "Reduce posting frequency to three times a week to align with engagement trends"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local bakery finds many people don’t see its posts, and the owner wants to drive more foot traffic. What’s a key advantage of using paid ads?",
    "answers": [
      "They can target users by location to increase nearby store visits"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer notices that unpaid posts are being shared, but overall reach remains low. What aspect of paid ads could help improve reach?",
    "answers": [
      "Paid ads display to the audience she selects, regardless of existing connections"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A consumer electronics brand wants to build awareness during a major tech event by sharing live updates, behind-the-scenes photos and real-time engagement. Which platform best supports this strategy?",
    "answers": [
      "X, which is ideal for real-time updates and event-based engagement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business is planning its first social media ad. What’s the first step to ensure relevance and success?",
    "answers": ["Define their target audience using demographics and interests"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small fitness brand wants to run its first ad campaign but is overwhelmed by audience options. What’s the best first step?",
    "answers": [
      "Define who their ideal customer is before selecting platform settings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An eco-friendly cleaning brand wants users to download a free guide on non-toxic cleaning. Which CTA is most effective for this ad?",
    "answers": ["“Download Now” to prompt immediate access to the guide"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team creates strong ad visuals, but conversions are low. They discovered that the landing page messaging was inconsistent with the ad. What does this reveal?",
    "answers": [
      "Assets must be coordinated to create a consistent experience from ad to action"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An artist wants to expand their reach to art enthusiasts in a specific city. Why would paid ads be more effective than organic content?",
    "answers": ["They allow geographic targeting regardless of follower status"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An ad receives a lot of views but few conversions. What might be missing?",
    "answers": ["A clear and compelling call to action"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A meal delivery brand is launching a campaign in urban neighborhoods to reach young professionals interested in quick, healthy dinners. What targeting filter would be most effective?",
    "answers": ["Location, age range and interest in healthy eating"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two companies are bidding for the same audience. One wins the auction, even with a slightly lower bid. Why?",
    "answers": [
      "Their ad had stronger relevance and quality scores for that audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A nonprofit organization runs a campaign encouraging people to sign up for a newsletter. The team wants to assess the cost of each new signup. Which KPI would be the best fit?",
    "answers": ["Cost per lead"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A skincare company receives a photo from a customer showing how they use the product at home and wants to feature it in an ad. What should the company do before using this image in their campaign?",
    "answers": ["Ask for permission before using the customer’s content"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media manager is working with a copywriter, designer and brand marketer to create a campaign for a product launch. Which reason best explains why collaborating with internal teams supports a strong ad campaign?",
    "answers": [
      "Internal teams bring specialized skills that create brand consistency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A freelance copywriter receives a creative brief from a client’s marketing team. It includes background about the campaign, audience insights, tone and examples of competitor messaging. How does the creative brief help the copywriter?",
    "answers": [
      "It provides clear direction for writing copy that aligns with the campaign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business owner creates two different image ads for the same product: one showing a close-up and another showing a lifestyle scene. What is the best next step to improve the campaign’s performance?",
    "answers": [
      "Run both versions and test which version gets better engagement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A digital wellness brand wants to get people to click their ad and visit the website. They’re exploring ways to spark curiosity in the ad copy. Which approach would most effectively create curiosity?",
    "answers": [
      "Use a question or fact that addresses a key customer challenge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media ad promotes a free trial of a new software tool, but the key message highlights customer testimonials instead of the trial offer. Why might this message be less effective?",
    "answers": [
      "It doesn’t directly support the campaign’s goal of driving trial signups"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A new ad uses a plain background and minimal color contrast. The team is concerned that users might scroll past it. What could help improve the ad’s performance?",
    "answers": [
      "Use brighter colors and stronger contrast to attract attention"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A beverage company runs a campaign to raise awareness for a new sparkling water line. The marketing team needs a metric that measures how well the ad is remembered. Which KPI should they use?",
    "answers": ["Ad recall lift"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer is drafting Facebook ad copy to promote a free trial of a meditation app. They want to hook readers, explain the benefit and prompt them to act. Which approach best follows a recommended copywriting structure?",
    "answers": ["Write an opening, a transition and a clear call to action"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media specialist is planning posts for an upcoming campaign. Some posts focus on engaging existing followers, while others need to drive website traffic from new users. How should they decide which posts should be paid?",
    "answers": [
      "Use paid ads when you want to reach beyond your current followers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A small business runs an ad with a photo of their product being used by a smiling customer. The copy highlights how the product improves daily routines. Why is this a strong example of ad design?",
    "answers": ["The image and text reinforce the same emotional benefit"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business tests different headlines for a campaign focused on boosting app downloads. One version emphasizes features, and the other emphasizes time savings. How should they evaluate which version works best?",
    "answers": [
      "Measure results based on which version leads to more downloads"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand tests two versions of an image: one with a product shot and another with a lifestyle scene. The lifestyle version performs better. What should they do next?",
    "answers": [
      "Use the better-performing image in the next phase of the campaign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fashion retailer is planning an ad for running shoes. Instead of placing the ad on sports blogs, they target users based on recent search history for workout gear. What advertising method are they using?",
    "answers": ["Data-based advertising"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing analyst is reviewing user data collected from interactions such as clicks, page visits and purchases. Why is this data valuable to both publishers and advertisers?",
    "answers": ["It allows ads and content to be personalized for the user"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After visiting an online clothing store, a user returns days later and sees items still in their shopping cart. What made this possible?",
    "answers": ["A cookie saves information in their browser"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An online furniture retailer shares its customer purchase history with a trusted home decor partner as part of a business agreement. What type of data is being shared?",
    "answers": ["Second-party data"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A group of advertisers voluntarily agrees to follow privacy standards set by an industry organization. What level of data protection does this represent?",
    "answers": ["Industry self-regulation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A California resident requests a copy of all the personal information a company has collected about them. What law gives them this right?",
    "answers": ["CCPA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand commits to the principles of notice, user choice and data security when serving ads. What is the benefit of following this self-regulatory framework?",
    "answers": ["It builds trust with consumers and promotes ethical data use"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser submits a campaign to Meta. Before approving the ad, the system checks the images, targeting and landing page. What policy is this process enforcing?",
    "answers": ["Meta’s advertising policy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A user clears their cookies and notices the website no longer remembers their shopping preferences. What privacy-sensitive feature was affected?",
    "answers": ["Local browser storage"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A digital marketing firm collects user behavior from multiple unrelated websites using tracking cookies, then sells that data to advertisers. What kind of data collection is this?",
    "answers": ["Third-party data"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team finds that their data-driven ad campaign received five times more engagement than a generic campaign. What does this suggest about using personal data?",
    "answers": ["It can significantly improve ad performance"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An athletic apparel company wants to reach adults aged 25–50 interested in fitness. What is the best method to define this audience in the Facebook ad setup?",
    "answers": [
      "Use detailed targeting to choose age, interests, and behaviors"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Once a campaign has a destination, audience, budget and duration, what is the final action before launch?",
    "answers": ["Submit the promotion for review"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A user sees an ad while viewing their friend's Stories. It appears between two Story posts. What kind of ad is this?",
    "answers": ["Instagram Stories ad"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A music streaming app tests their story ad with and without a voice-over. The version with sound performs better. What does this show?",
    "answers": ["Enhance your story with sound"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer selects a one-day campaign with a $100 budget. What effect does this combination likely have?",
    "answers": [
      "The ad will attempt to reach many users quickly, possibly resulting in faster spend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A boutique owner isn’t sure who to target, but wants to launch quickly. Which targeting strategy is best?",
    "answers": ["Let Instagram optimize delivery using Suggested Audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A jewelry brand uses a product image and a \"Shop Now\" CTA in a Story ad focused on sales. What part of the funnel is this creative aligned with?",
    "answers": [
      "Bottom of the funnel, because it aims to convert viewers into buyers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing intern wants to post a Story that lasts longer than 24 hours. Why might she use a paid ad instead of an organic post?",
    "answers": [
      "Paid Stories can run longer than 24 hours and appear in ad placements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A digital marketer is setting up an ad from their business’s Facebook Business Page to attract people to their website for a summer sale. What should be his first action after clicking the “Promote” button?",
    "answers": ["Select “Get More Website Visitors” from the list of ad goals"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A startup wants to grow its newsletter email list using Facebook ads. What objective should they choose?",
    "answers": ["Get More Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An apparel company posts a story with five quick scenes over ten seconds. What tactic are they using?",
    "answers": ["Split your story into scenes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "While reviewing her ad draft, a user noticed Facebook had pre-filled the headline and image from her last post. What is the advantage of changing these default elements?",
    "answers": [
      "Custom creative makes the ad more relevant to the audience and goal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing analyst at a startup sets their Instagram promotion to run for two days with a $5 daily budget. How does this impact their campaign?",
    "answers": [
      "The ad will run for 48 hours and spend up to $10 total, reaching a smaller audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A junior marketer wants to focus on users aged 18–24 who live in Boston and follow fashion brands. What is the best way to set up targeting?",
    "answers": ["Use Create Your Own to define age, location, and interests"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to create a single campaign that runs on Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, and the Audience Network. Which tool should be used to enable this multi-platform distribution?",
    "answers": ["Meta Ads Manager web interface"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team wants its video ad to run during video content on Facebook, placed alongside videos from trusted publishers. Which placement should they use?",
    "answers": ["In-Stream"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser is setting up a new Meta campaign. Which level should they use to choose the campaign’s goal?",
    "answers": ["Campaign"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to ensure its ad runs only during peak hours when users are most active. Where can they control this setting?",
    "answers": ["Within the ad set under “Schedule” options"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question prompt goes hereA business owner needs to check ad performance and make quick edits to campaigns while traveling. Which Ads Manager tool is best suited for this?",
    "answers": ["Ads Manager mobile app"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser sees that their ad is losing auctions despite a competitive bid. Which factor could be reducing the ad’s total value?",
    "answers": ["The ad quality score is low due to poor user experience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser wants to ensure that total ad costs do not exceed a set budget. What tool should be used to prevent spending beyond a fixed amount?",
    "answers": ["Set an account spending limit in the Payment Settings section"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser has a high estimated action rate but poor ad quality. What effect might this have in the Meta ad auction?",
    "answers": [
      "It could lower the total value and reduce the chances of winning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to adjust settings like billing information, payment methods, and account security. Which section of the navigation bar in Meta Ads Manager should they use?",
    "answers": ["Manage Business"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser is deciding how much they’re willing to spend for each website visit. What does this amount represent in Meta’s auction system?",
    "answers": ["Their advertiser bid"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local business wants to collect contact information from people who may be interested in scheduling a consultation. Which Meta campaign objective should be selected to support this strategy?",
    "answers": ["Leads"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign uses a lifetime budget and is set to run for 10 days. How does Meta determine how much to spend each day?",
    "answers": ["Meta adjusts daily spend automatically based on opportunities"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser is unsure how to divide their budget between several ad sets. They want Meta to handle the distribution automatically. Which budget option supports this approach?",
    "answers": ["Campaign Budget Optimization"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants to drive traffic to its website so people can learn about a flower subscription service. What objective should be used?",
    "answers": ["Traffic"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An interior design company wants to attract more likes, comments, and shares on their new social media campaign. What campaign objective should they choose?",
    "answers": ["Engagement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser wants to make sure no more than $20 is spent each day, even if there are opportunities for higher performance. Which budget type should be used?",
    "answers": ["Daily budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A mobile app company is preparing to launch a new budgeting app and wants to drive as many installs as possible. Which campaign objective is the best match?",
    "answers": ["App promotion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign has a daily budget of $60. On high-opportunity days, Meta may spend up to how much in a single day?",
    "answers": ["$75"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign is using a lifetime budget of $300 over 10 days. How does Meta distribute the budget across those days?",
    "answers": ["Meta can spend more on some days and less on others"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A home décor brand is running a sale and wants to drive people directly to its online store to make purchases. Which campaign objective is the best fit?",
    "answers": ["Sales"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to create a new audience based on people who previously interacted with their app. What should they use as a source to build a lookalike audience?",
    "answers": ["Custom Audience based on app activity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to create an audience based on specific demographics, interests, and behaviors. What type of audience should they use?",
    "answers": ["Core audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to re-engage people who visited their site more than 60 days ago but haven’t returned. What should they use to retarget this group?",
    "answers": ["Create a time-based website Custom Audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client is deciding between letting Meta choose placements or selecting them manually. What is one benefit of using Advantage+ placements?",
    "answers": [
      "It automatically delivers ads in the most cost-effective placements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to run their campaign continuously starting today without setting an end date. What should they do in Ads Manager?",
    "answers": ["Choose a start date and leave the end date blank"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to understand whether their ad settings are too narrow. What can they review in Ads Manager to help with this?",
    "answers": ["The estimated audience size tool"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants their ad to appear only during weekday afternoons for a short promotional campaign. What type of budget allows this level of scheduling control?",
    "answers": ["Lifetime budget"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client asks to show ads to people based on their hobbies and device usage. Which feature of core audiences allows this level of targeting?",
    "answers": ["Interests and behaviors targeting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company has installed the Meta Pixel and wants to use the data to measure conversions in their campaign. What additional step must they take?",
    "answers": ["Connect the Pixel to their ad account in Ads Manager"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants to reach people based on their interests, location, and behavior patterns. Which audience type should they choose?",
    "answers": ["Core audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A client wants their campaign to generate as many purchases as possible. Which optimization strategy should they select?",
    "answers": ["Optimize for conversions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company wants its ads to run only during specific hours of the day, such as evenings. Which scheduling option should they select?",
    "answers": ["Use a lifetime budget and schedule specific times"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants users to visit its website and browse new products. What choice will best guide Meta in optimizing the ad delivery for this intent?",
    "answers": ["Selecting a Traffic campaign objective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A clothing store wants to showcase several items from its new collection in a single ad to increase product awareness. Which ad format should they choose to meet this goal?",
    "answers": ["Carousel"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser uploads a product photo and sees options to crop it into square, vertical, or horizontal shapes. Why should these cropping tools be used?",
    "answers": ["To optimize how the image appears across different placements"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A skincare company wants to run an ad stating “Erase all acne in 7 days.” Which policy concern is most relevant here?",
    "answers": ["Prohibited exaggerated or misleading claims"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser wants to ensure that a campaign spends evenly over time without exceeding a set total. Which option in Ads Manager supports this objective?",
    "answers": ["Use a lifetime budget with standard delivery"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team wants to compare how different demographics responded to an ad quickly. What feature in Ads Manager supports this?",
    "answers": ["Breakdown by audience attributes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser selects “Traffic” as the campaign objective. What result metric will most likely be tracked?",
    "answers": ["Link clicks"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An ad is being created for a local gardening workshop with the goal of increasing sign-ups for an upcoming event. Which step in Ads Manager helps ensure the ad aligns with this marketing goal?",
    "answers": [
      "Selecting the appropriate campaign objective for lead generation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A business wants to create a new ad from scratch with a single image and original ad copy. Which action should be taken first in the creative section?",
    "answers": ["Choose the ad format as “Single Image”"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser includes “You will gain muscle fast!” in the ad copy. Why is this likely to be rejected?",
    "answers": ["It makes a personal attribute claim"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign’s ad set is marked “Learning Limited” due to not achieving enough optimization events. What is the best way to help the ad set exit this status?",
    "answers": [
      "Raise the budget to ensure at least 50 conversion events per week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser wants to see how the cost per result has changed over several weeks. What should be done?",
    "answers": ["Use the Breakdown feature to segment by week"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You’ve launched a campaign with multiple ad sets and want to monitor the performance of a single ad set. Where should you go in Ads Manager to find this information?",
    "answers": ["The Ad Sets tab within Ads Manager"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A candy company creates a campaign to increase sales of its candies through its website. Which metric should the company use to evaluate the success of the campaign?",
    "answers": ["Sales"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which feature is available for an unpaid (organic) post on a Page?",
    "answers": ["Add a video"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two ad placement platforms are available when you create an ad in Ads Manager? (Choose two)",
    "answers": ["Instagram Feed", "Audience Insights"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser is about to deliver a campaign. Where should the advertiser navigate to in Ads Manager to include Instagram in the campaign?",
    "answers": ["Ad set level"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local gym spends $1,000 on ads to promote its new membership program. Over the next month, the campaign generates 50 leads. The gym typically converts 20% of leads into paying members; each new member brings in $500 annually. What is the ROAS?",
    "answers": ["5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A subscription box service charges $50/month, with an average customer lifespan of 24 months and one purchase per month. What is the Lifetime Value?",
    "answers": ["$1,200"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing manager is reviewing two recent campaigns. One campaign has a ROAS of 4, and the other has a ROAS of 2. However, the campaign with the lower ROAS generated more profit. What is the most likely explanation?",
    "answers": ["The second campaign had lower production or fulfillment costs"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team runs two campaigns. One has a cost per result of $5, the other $20. Without additional context, what should they do?",
    "answers": [
      "Review how much each result is actually worth before making a decision"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A local gym runs a campaign that costs $2,400 and brings in 60 new members. What is their CAC?",
    "answers": ["$40"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which metric would be most helpful in understanding the long-term revenue a customer might generate for your company?",
    "answers": ["Lifetime Value (LTV)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An online learning company earns $12,000 in revenue from a campaign with $4,000 in ad and operations costs. What is the ROI?",
    "answers": ["2.0"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign has a ROAS of 5. What insight does this provide to a marketing manager?",
    "answers": ["The revenue was five times the amount spent on advertising"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team compares two campaigns: one shows a strong ROAS but weak ROI, while the other has moderate ROAS and strong ROI. The team wants to prioritize campaigns that lead to long-term profitability. Which metric should they focus on?",
    "answers": [
      "ROI, because it includes all investments and provides a clearer picture of profit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer notices that their campaign has a cost per lead of $50. Each lead typically converts into a $2,000 client. What does this suggest?",
    "answers": [
      "The cost per lead is reasonable, given the value of a converted customer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "During a Brand Lift Test, the percentage of people in the control group who recalled the ad was 7.9%, and in the test group it was 21.8%. What should the marketer conclude from these numbers?",
    "answers": [
      "There is a 13.9 point increase in brand recall between test and control groups"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a recent Brand Lift Test, 11% of the control group indicated that they remembered seeing the ad, even though they were not targeted with it. What is the most appropriate explanation for this recall in the control group?",
    "answers": [
      "Respondents may recall the brand due to prior exposure or perceived familiarity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign shows promising test results, but the confidence level is too low to be considered reliable. The team wants to improve the setup for future experiments. How can they increase the confidence level in the next test?",
    "answers": ["Extend the test duration to collect more responses"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign manager wants to exclude users from the test group if they don’t see the ad. A colleague recommends keeping them in to reduce bias. Why is it important to keep participants in their original group assignment under ITT?",
    "answers": ["It preserves randomization and minimizes selection bias"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer is launching a new campaign to improve awareness of a brand’s online ordering option. The goal is to increase recognition among a broader audience. Which test should the marketer use to evaluate this campaign’s effectiveness?",
    "answers": ["Brand Lift Test"]
  },
  {
    "question": "While setting up a survey for a Brand Lift Test, a marketer wants to ensure the poll questions are relevant to the campaign. How can the marketer ensure the questions align with the campaign’s content?",
    "answers": [
      "Customize the wording of the ad recall question to match the ad and brand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brand’s test results show similar lift values to the regional benchmark, but leadership is unsure how to use the data. What is a meaningful way to act on this result?",
    "answers": ["Use the comparison to guide expectations for future campaigns"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A Brand Lift Test reports 26% ad recall in the test group and 11% in the control group. How should the brand lift be calculated based on these results?",
    "answers": [
      "Subtract the control group’s recall from the test group’s recall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign generates strong conversion results, but the ROAS is lower than expected. The team wants to improve future spend efficiency. Which strategy could help improve ROAS in future campaigns?",
    "answers": [
      "Shift more budget toward campaigns that show proven performance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing analyst is reviewing how test groups were managed in a brand lift experiment. They learn that participants remained in their assigned groups regardless of whether they saw the ad. What principle does this approach reflect?",
    "answers": ["Intention to Treat"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team sets up a Brand Lift Test but begins running their campaign before launching the experiment. Why is this a problem for valid test results?",
    "answers": [
      "The control group must be defined before any ad exposure occurs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After analyzing test results, a marketer learns that their campaign produced positive lift, but only for a specific audience segment. What is one way to use this insight to refine future campaigns?",
    "answers": [
      "Adjust targeting to focus on the segment that responded most positively"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing director is reviewing a campaign's annual performance across TV, Facebook, and YouTube. They want to understand which channel contributed most to sales. Which approach would help them determine the contribution of each channel to the final results?",
    "answers": [
      "Use Media Mix Modeling to analyze past data and evaluate each channel's ROI"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer wants to evaluate which of their ads played the most crucial role in a customer’s decision to make a purchase. What is the primary purpose of attribution modeling in this context?",
    "answers": [
      "To assign credit to specific touchpoints that influenced a customer’s conversion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An advertiser collects data from their app, website, and retail store, but finds it difficult to attribute all actions to a single user. What makes it hard to connect these touchpoints?",
    "answers": [
      "Reliance on cookies, which are ineffective across mobile and apps"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A social media team wants to run an A/B test comparing two ad headlines. To ensure the test delivers reliable insights, what is one best practice they should follow?",
    "answers": ["Test only one variable at a time"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company uses a last-click attribution model but notices that early ads in the funnel aren’t being credited for conversions. What is one limitation of this model?",
    "answers": [
      "It ignores the influence of earlier touchpoints in the customer journey"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team uses available performance data to identify which ads had the greatest incremental impact on conversions. What is a key feature of statistical attribution models?",
    "answers": [
      "They assign fractional credit to touchpoints based on estimated incremental impact"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A media planner receives attribution data showing high ROI for search and social ads, but low ROI for display ads. What is the most strategic response?",
    "answers": [
      "Reallocate budget to channels with higher ROI for the next quarter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team wants to track app purchases, website sales, and in-store transactions in one reporting system. Which tools should they use to capture these data sources on Meta?",
    "answers": ["Meta Pixel, SDK, and Conversions API"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A company is running a cross-platform holiday campaign that includes digital, print, and TV. They want to evaluate which channels to prioritize next year. Why would Media Mix Modeling be appropriate in this situation?",
    "answers": [
      "It’s designed to measure the effectiveness of both online and offline media channels"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A strategist wants to distribute credit equally across all ad impressions and clicks that led to a purchase. Which attribution model should they choose?",
    "answers": ["Even-credit attribution model"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An analyst is unsure whether to use a rules-based or statistical model. What is one advantage of using a statistical model over a rules-based model?",
    "answers": [
      "It reflects actual performance patterns rather than relying on assumptions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A team is preparing an A/B test and wants to ensure the results clearly show which change made the difference. What is the most important step in designing the test?",
    "answers": ["Vary only one element between the two ad versions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An analyst is reviewing attribution results for a brand awareness campaign. The data shows strong impact from early impressions. What model would best reflect this influence?",
    "answers": ["First-touch attribution model"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After an A/B test, a manager assumes the ad with the highest click-through rate is the winner. However, it also had a higher cost per result. What should the manager consider before concluding?",
    "answers": [
      "The goal of the test and which metric aligns best with campaign objectives"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team is presenting campaign results and wants to help the audience evaluate success. What role do campaign goals play in this part of the presentation?",
    "answers": [
      "They provide a baseline for measuring whether the results met expectations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A campaign team is preparing a performance presentation and wants the audience to notice the key metric first. What is the best way to help the audience focus on what matters?",
    "answers": ["Use color contrast to highlight the most critical data point"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team reviews campaign data and notices that most sales happened in the second half of the month. How should this finding be used to improve the next campaign?",
    "answers": [
      "Shift more ad budget to the part of the month when sales are higher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketer feels nervous before starting and wants to center themselves. What technique could help provide calm and focus before speaking?",
    "answers": [
      "Take a deep breath or sip water as a calming anchor before starting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing coordinator is preparing to present in a conference room they haven’t used before. What should be done in advance to avoid technical issues?",
    "answers": [
      "Check how to load their presentation on the room’s computer or screen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An A/B test reveals that one creative performed significantly better than the other. What conclusion should be drawn from this data?",
    "answers": [
      "Use the better-performing creative for future campaigns and continue testing other options"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A presenter is concluding a campaign performance presentation and wants to leave the audience with a strong final message. What is the best way to conclude the presentation?",
    "answers": [
      "Circle back to their opening by answering their initial question or finishing their story"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing team preparing for a campaign presentation wants to feel confident about the timing and flow. What should be done before presenting?",
    "answers": [
      "Practice the entire presentation out loud and time how long it takes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A chart showing sales growth starts the vertical axis at 100 instead of 0, making the growth appear larger than it really is. What adjustment should be made?",
    "answers": [
      "Adjust the axis to start at zero so the visual accurately reflects the change in data"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing campaign team wants to show that their results were carefully tested before sharing conclusions. What could be mentioned to explain the process?",
    "answers": [
      "Describe any experiments, such as an A/B test, that were used to validate the results"
    ]
  }
]
